Aloha!
I remember the words you taught me a long time ago.
Aloha oe.
Do you remember?
Do you know Hawaii?
Yes, I do.
Do you know where Hawaii is?
What kind of place is it?
It's over there.
There's a lot of papayas.
There are palm trees and palm trees.
It's a warm country.
You can say aloha.
Look.
Aloha!
With that in mind, let's have a good time today.
Have a good time!
Aloha.
I'm a housewife.
I'm hungry.
Good morning.
Mr. Hitoshi Mikami!
Let's buy a bed!
Today, we're going to find out how to buy Hyomontokage-modoki.
Shomon and Kagemotoki live in the desert.
They eat insects and other insects.
When they grow up, they are about 30cm tall.
The water tank is about 60cm long.
A 60cm water tank.
Since we live in a desert area, we need a heater.
Make sure it's between 25 and 30 degrees.
It warms you up to about 5 degrees.
We also built a place where we can take a day off and go to the sun.
I need a hiding place.
The place to stay is upside down.
In the summer, you can bring them here and eat them.
When there's no food in winter, we sell corgis at pet shops.
I'll give it a try.
I'll give you insects such as crickets!
If you win the game with Osumiya, you may have children.
It's fun.
Don't know how to do that.
Mama.
Wow.
Thank you.
Tosa no mo, tosa no mo, tosa no mo, ha!
Aiya, aiya, deyai, deyai, appareja, appareja!
What is it?
I made a good one.
Oh, you scared me.
I didn't know you were such a great person.
Nothing.
Can you see this?
What's this?
I'm sorry.
This is for you.
That's right.
Why do you have that seal?
I made it.
What?
Did you make it?
Yes.
There's something written on it.
Yeah.
What does it say?
I don't know what it says.
Hey, if you want to peel off the sticker cleanly, you need to pour vinegar.
When I walk in the city, I see young people using things they don't understand.
They use computers.
I know you're a cousin, but what is a computer?
It's not a cousin, it's a cousin.
Computer!
I've done it before.
What does it mean?
I don't know.
I see.
It's difficult.
That's what it means.
And the young ones were talking to each other, so I listened to them.
Then, the lord said, seriously, you're so lame.
Then, with this dog,
It's better to say that you can't see a dog.
That's right.
Then, Master, come to my castle.
He said, let's have the characters scratch their necks.
That's a pretty bold thing to say.
We have a lot of work to do!
That's right!
Today's work is to be a meteorologist.
My job is to bend a glass can and make a Japanese sign.
I'm a Japanese artist.
The sign that glitters at night is very beautiful.
The sign is a piece of glass called neon.
It's very difficult to bend glass.
If you don't bend it at the right time, it will break.
However, Mr. Nihonkan Gikoshi can bend any difficult shape.
Why is it so easy to bend?
If you let air in through your mouth, the glass will...
That's because Mr. Gikoushi of Neon-Kan knows it
I made a neon that matches the red flag!
Ugo Ugo!
Yeah!
I did it!
When you put special gas into the glass can, it turns red When you put another gas, it turns blue
Darken the surroundings and switch on!
Look!
I made such a beautiful neon sign!
Ya!
Ugo Ugo Lula!
You can make a big neon sign like this
This is the work of a Neon Kanji instructor!
Wow!
It's beautiful!
The second part of Hardy's story, Tess.
In Tess's house, where no one works,
and she was the only one who relied on him.
So, Tess changed her father into a drunkard and started working as a helper at her relative's house.
No matter how hard it was, Tess worked hard for the sake of her family.
One day, Alec, the son of the housekeeper, was invited.
Everyone likes you, baby.
I was wondering what to do next.
I was going to give him a baby, but unfortunately, the baby died right away.
Hurry up and say the words of your father's country.
I'm going to say it at the end.
Don't rush.
And can you answer my question?
Yes.
I said, the lord is really lame, but I don't know what it means.
I was happy to praise him.
What does that mean?
Dasaai means...
I don't know.
I got it!
What is it?
That means I'm not popular.
You!
It's Ugo Ugo Luger!
Please teach me one of my country's words.
Okay.
Is that okay?
Yes.
Thank you.
That's very kind of you.
I have a word to say when you're in trouble.
Say, what is it?
What is it?
Mr. Ishii always says that.
Did you know it at first?
I know it.
I don't know it.
What do you mean by you don't know it?
You say you don't know.
Ah, I see.
There are many ways to say it.
When you are in trouble, you use the word 偉い.
That's a good one.
You know what?
What?
You just said it out loud, right?
What's wrong with that?
I won't do anything.
That's right.
One day as a runner.
Ozen, you don't even have a job, but you practice in the company.
You don't get fired easily.
Ooga, ooga, ooga.
Mikan Seijin has appeared.
Thank you.
I often do it like this.
Do it like this.
I did it again!
This is what you do when you're in trouble.
No.
This is what you do when you're thinking.
Hey, Mr.
Tone!
What?
Why do you have one tooth when you laugh?
Go to the dentist.
I'm gonna cry again.
I'm always being swayed by you guys, so when that happens, all I can do is say, I'm sorry.
Got it?
I don't think I've heard it clearly.
Anyway, I want you to remember that.
I got it.
Yes.
I'll invite you to my castle soon.
That's right.
This is rare, so please look forward to it.
See you later!
Bye-bye!
A date in the fall!
I'm going to eat you alive!
I'm from China!
I have Udon!
Now, you two have become good at the language of the country of the lord, haven't you?
Yes.
This is called learning rather than learning.
It's better to get used to it than to learn it.
Yes.
It's better to get used to it than to learn it than to learn it.
Do you understand?
Yes.
All right.
See you later.
Bye-bye.
Me ga dete kita yo
Choo-choo, ka-ka.
Chichi-ka-ka, chichi-ka-ka, chika-chika-chin.
Futago's father and mother
Shippo ga toreta
Eat your food and evolve