Good morning.
Good morning. Good morning.
Good morning. Good morning. Good morning.
Both Ugo and Ruga are awake.
Yes!
Say that again.
This is too long!
Hide the seven boys.
Even if you're sleepy, you're cute because you're white.
So, have a good day.
Gokuraku Akiraku Gokuraku
Who are you?
I'm Pandas!
Ooga, ooga, ooga
Thank you for watching!
Who woke you up, Buhi?
Oh, it's dirty, Buhi!
I'm going to pee, Buhi!
No, Buhi!
Go, Buhi!
First, let's sing our favorite song.
Nikuman?
Oh, no, not Nikuman.
Buhi, let's start with Budo.
Buhi, it's Budo.
Oh.
What do you think?
Do you want to try it?
Cow!
Wow!
Next is Uwagodabuhi.
Shikadabuhi.
Jinn.
Jimmie!
Good morning.
Mr. Katsuhiko Sato of Tokyo University, the great man of the universe.
Today, I would like to talk about how far the stars are from each other.
The distance between the stars
You all know that Molly went to space on a space shuttle, right?
But the universe that Mr. Mori went to was the one that circled around the Earth.
The universe is actually much wider.
For example, in order to know the direction,
You can see the distance by looking at the North Pole.
How far do you think the North Pole is?
This is about 400 light years away.
In other words, it takes 400 light years.
The distance is 7.5 laps per second.
It takes a year to reach such a fast distance.
What I'm trying to say is that the Hokkyokusei you're watching now
In fact, it is a 400-year-old figure.
The universe is so big that it can take light years to reach it.
Asano-bun-gaku Iho-ji, Episode 1
One day, Murusou heard that his mother had died and ran to her.
Everyone in the room was sad and crying.
However, Muruso doesn't look sad at all when he sees his mother's dead body.
He seems to be very bored by drinking and sleeping.
And Murusawa went out of the room as if nothing had happened.
Next.
FIGHT!
I'm Hoshigamuhi.
Chinchin.
Huh?
What's that?
Kinko?
Yeah, kinko.
Yeah.
Koko.
Kodama.
Eh?
Kodama?
So that way.
Mwah.
What?
It's a cow.
A cow?
Huh?
What?
A cow?
Huh?
Is that a cow?
Yeah, it's a cow.
Over here.
Cut the video.
No!
But, Karu, we're so tired.
I'm so tired.
My brother's so tired.
Well then, we're going home.
Why?
Well then, bye-bye!
Bye-bye!
I have a lot of work to do!
When I go to a restaurant, I don't know what to eat.
I think you'll know what you want to eat as soon as you have a recipe.
Our job is to make such a recipe.
This is called ROU.
This ROU is used to make ROU.
This is used to make food.
Let's make one of your favorites.
Do you know what's going to happen?
Looks like it's done It looks like real pudding
No, it's wonderful!
Next, let's see his best technique.
It looks like an amoeba floating on water.
What will the green wolf transform into?
I don't know
This is exactly the same as the real lettuce.
Well done.
Let's see how real it is.
It's perfect!
This is also a food sample made by him.
Simply put, it's the food of Japan.
Wrap it gently like this.
The tempura looks more delicious than the real one This is the job of a food sample craftsman
If you read a book on the road... ...you'll get hit by a car!
Where are you from?
I'm French.
The first one is round and round and round and round
Absorbs and evolves The tail stretches
Me ga dete kita yo
Chichi Kaka, Chichi Kaka, Chichi Kaka.
Chichi Kaka, Chichi Kaka, Chichi Kachin.
Futago no chichi to kaka Shippo ga tore
Eat food and evolve.