Good morning.
Oh, it's upside down.
Ugo and Luga, if you get a bad score in the school test, will you keep whining?
No, we won't.
I'll tell you exactly what we're going to say.
Okay?
Okay.
The wind will blow tomorrow.
Tomorrow will be another stormy day.
Yes.
They say they failed, but they can't help it.
They're determined to work hard tomorrow.
It's a very easy word.
Remember it.
Yes.
Okiraku gokuraku!
Yes, yes.
Who are you?
I'm Harapeko Daisaku.
I'll be waiting for you in January.
Good morning.
Hikari Hito Mikami Hitoshi Sensei Hikari Hito Kaoru
Today, we're going to find a common fish.
How to buy Hyomoon Rikusame Hyomoon Rikusame is an African grassland desert.
The male is about 50 cm and the female is about 70 cm.
We have a 60-centimeter tank for you.
A 60-centimeter tank?
I live in a warm place, so I need a heater.
I set it to about 25 degrees.
I'll warm it up to about 25 degrees.
You need a place where you can play in the sun, so you can put a light bulb there.
Let's make a warm place.
I like to cook with water, so I'd like to add something that can be cooked with water.
I'll make something that can be cooked with water.
Soba.
It's an ornament, so there are vegetables like cabbage and pumpkin.
I'd like you to try some banana-like fruits.
You don't have to change the water in the aquarium.
It's easy to change.
Give it a try.
Toh no hakubu-san!
Bye-bye!
I always end up falling apart, so everyone calls me a robot.
I'm a little sad, so I want to do my best.
We look forward to working with you.
What's the big deal?
I got it!
What?
Uga-Uga-Kan. A company!
I see.
It's big, isn't it?
But there are small companies, too.
Wait, wait, wait.
My answer is big.
Don't break it by yourself.
If you leave the burnt bread in the fridge, it will become smelly.
Go, Go, Lula!
Give me a seat!
Let's go!
Okay!
Um, Ugo Ugo, how big are your shoes?
Are you awake?
You're still sleeping, aren't you?
One hundred!
One hundred?
No way!
Nineteen!
Nineteen centimeters.
But you know, if you put something like this in the shape of a shoe, it'll fit perfectly.
But if you don't put it in, it'll get soggy.
21!
And then, the shoes.
If the shoes are small, they become old.
If that's the answer...
I'm sorry.
I have a lot of work to do!
That's right!
Today's work is a mask craftsman.
My job is to make masks for pro wrestlers.
I'm a mask maker.
This is a special cloth that can only be stretched sideways.
Only the mask craftsman can make a mask that cannot be torn or torn.
Especially around the eyes, it is easy to tear, so sew it carefully.
Make sure you match the parts you made to your head.
Perfect!
Great job!
The coolest part of Thunder Liger's mask is this horn.
The mask craftsman knows how to make it look cool.
When the mask is ready, he will wear it himself to make sure.
Jyushin Thunder Liger is here.
How is it?
It looks strong, doesn't it?
No, it's great.
This is the job of a mask craftsman!
Put on the mask again!
The Literature of the Day!
Hardy's Tests, Episode 4
After Claire left him, Ruth waited for him to come back.
However, the misfortune of her father's death again attacks her.
Father's fool!
Onee-chan, I'm hungry.
For the family who were more and more troubled by life, it was only possible to take care of that Aleph again.
Even though a tree is a tree, what tree grows in the stomach?
It's difficult.
What's in your stomach?
My heart and my heart.
I don't know.
I don't have time to answer your questions.
There's no such thing as no time.
It feels good.
I'll give you an answer.
Okay.
Don't say, hurry, hurry.
The tree that grows in your stomach
My name is Ichou.
Why?
I have to explain.
What are you doing?
Sato-san and Yamada-san were there.
When I told Sato-san and Yamada-san that I was going out, who went out first?
Sato-san!
Why?
Why, Sato-san?
Sato-san is a woman.
Yes, a woman.
Why?
And what about Yamada-san?
Yamada-san is also a woman.
No, no, no.
Tell me why.
Nakada-san?
Nakada-san isn't here.
With Sato-san!
Sato-san, what are you doing?
Isn't that Satsuma-chan?
No, it's not.
You can't do that in the middle.
Sato-san!
Sato-san, that's the right answer.
But why?
Sato means... Sato...
Hold it in your hand and shake it.
If you shake it and put your hand in front of it, it's faster.
One day, a runner... Nobunaga is ready to compete with a car.
Mikan Seijin appears.
The answer is Mr. Sato.
Yay!
Sato?
I don't think you know the answer.
Yes?
What was the meaning of that?
When Sato-san said he was going,
Mr. Yamada said he couldn't go out yet.
I might have been fooled.
I'm so frustrated.
But I'll do my best this time, so you won't make fun of me.
I'll do my best!
Yeah!
Let's do our best, Ugaoka!
It was really exciting, so I'm going home.
I'm going home soon.
I'll do my best next time.
Well, bye-bye!
Bye-bye!
An Autumn Date
What if I eat Abe-kun's frozen meal?
Who is it?
From the morning onward, I'm going to kick your ass!
Today's theme is recycling.
Have you ever heard of recycling?
No.
What does it mean?
You can't throw it into the ocean.
Well, it's similar, but a little different.
Recycling is throwing something you've used once
and use it again in a different form.
In other words, the empty cans you put on paper today are also recycled.
Got it?
Yes.
It's an important word, so remember it.
That's all for today.
Bye-bye.
Go!
Choo-choo, caw-caw.
Chichi-ka-ka, Chichi-ka-ka, Chika-chika-chin.
Futago-no-chichi-to-ka-ka, Shippo-ra-to-ka-ka.
Kero kero kero kero Gohan o tabete sinka suru