Phew.
Today's TV show was about to fail.
Have you both failed?
Yes.
What kind of failure?
Well...
Hurry up and say it.
I spilled the egg.
That's a failure.
Today's phrase is, Failure is the mother of success.
Failure is the mother of success.
Very good.
If you fail a lot, you will succeed a lot someday.
Yes.
Did you remember?
Yes!
Well then, have fun today!
Have fun!
Well done!
Who are you?
Hello, I'm Emi Murai.
Oto no Hakubutsu-tan!
One, two, three.
It seems that if you put the finished teabag on your eyelids, you can get rid of the fatigue in your eyes.
One, two, three!
Uoguruga!
It won't be hard.
Who are you guys?
I'm scared.
Are you Ugo Ugo and Luger?
Yes.
It's a horn!
Oh, I see.
I thought it was different because horns are popular.
Full of work!
That's right!
Today's work is a shamisen craftsman.
My job is to make a instrument called a shamisen.
I am a shamisen craftsman.
Shamisen is an instrument made of three strings that have been in Japan for a long time.
The important thing to make a paper ship is to make a good river.
If you hold it with your feet and rub it hard, you can make a leather that is easy to handle.
The Shami-sen craftsman can tell if a good sound comes out just by looking at the face.
No, it's a success!
This is a seaweed made from rice.
It's been used for decades, so it's very strong.
He quickly hooks a thread on a tool like a large washing tweezers and sticks it on the skin.
Mr. Chami-sen doesn't let his guard down.
Well done!
Whether the sound is good or not is decided by the tension of the skin of the shamisen.
Shami-sen craftsman checks if it's well-dried and makes it.
I made a good-sounding shami-sen Great job!
This is the work of a Kamisen craftsman.
Amazing!
Then I heard that you guys are good at various things.
Sochi is...
It depends on where you listen to it.
What?
Sochi...
What do you think?
It's good.
Oh, really?
Can you teach me how to do it?
I put my hand in the gap.
I take it with my hand and put it in the net.
It's too fast, I don't get it.
What kind of gap is that?
Well, it's like this.
Well...
It's a gap.
That was fast, but you don't get it?
Maybe you've never caught a crayfish before?
I have!
Are you mad?
I knew it!
Asano Bungaku!
Minami Kaikisen!
Saishoukai!
On a cold night with beautiful stars, Mira and Mara were warming up their cold bodies in the bed.
However, their happiness did not last long.
Miller, who hated Mara, said goodbye to her.
However, while remembering that happy feeling, Miller strongly thought in his heart that he would do his best even if he was alone.
The End
One day as an ally of Sein.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23,
Is there anything you're good at?
Do you like movies?
Well... Dance?
Are you good at dancing?
Can you teach me how to dance well?
Do you shake your hips?
No, I shake my butt.
You shake your butt?
No, it's not.
Let's dance.
Don't shake your hips too much.
I see.
I have limited movement, so I can't go that far.
But I have a sense of rhythm.
Well, I'll have to practice.
Good!
Good morning.
Let's make it with flowers!
Today, let's make poplis.
Popri is a dried flower, and it has a very nice scent when it is in the room.
For example, I think it would be good to make it with the flowers when the flowers are wilted.
What we have here are flowers and aluminum foil.
Aluminum foil and flowers.
First, arrange the flowers and petals on the aluminum foil.
Arrange flowers and petals on aluminum foil.
Put this aluminum foil in the oven.
If it's a petal, 2 to 3 hours.
If it's a flower, 4 to 5 hours.
Dry at a temperature of about 60 to 70 degrees Dry in the oven
When you use an oven, ask your mother to use it with you.
Let's ask your mother to help us.
When it's done, put this pot in a bowl and sprinkle with your mother's perfume.
I think it will be very fragrant.
Then, the language of my country, well, this is a country in the west,
I will give you the word of the word.
Please teach me.
Is that okay?
Yes.
It's not just a word, but in our country, we call it OOKINI.
OOKINI!
Well, it's a pretty good line, but it's a bit emotional.
Try saying it like you're really grateful.
OOKINI!
I like it!
It's good, isn't it?
The language of my country is beautiful.
Not at all.
We're more beautiful.
What do you mean?
Say it.
Well...
What does it mean?
Thank you.
When I say I like it, it's as if I'm saying thank you and I like it.
Did you guys have a nosebleed?
Do you think you can have a nosebleed?
I do!
I see.
Now that you've come to your senses, let's get back to work and go home.
Okay.
This is difficult.
Okay, you can stop now.
I can't do this anymore.
Bye!
When you're doing your homework on the S-curve...
Ooga, ooga, ooga.
Ooga.
Who are you?
I'm a brave Russian.
Today on TV, I learned the language of the country of the lord.
Do you still remember?
The language of the country of the lord.
Obotara!
Yutte goran?
Oogini!
Hohohoho, daiseiko!
If you learn a lot of things, you'll have a lot of fun talking.
I hope you have a great day!
Great day!
Bye-bye!
Go!
Choo-choo-choo!
Chichi-ka-ka, chichi-ka-ka, chika-chika-chin.
Futago-no-chichi-to-ka-ka, shippora-to-ka.
Kero kero kero kero Gohan wo tabete shinka suru
Thanks for watching!