Mint.
Oh no, they're both upside down.
Good morning.
I picked up a dunghill this morning.
Have you ever picked up a dunghill?
Yes.
Where?
It's my backyard park.
I see, I see.
Have you ever picked it up, Ruga?
I have!
You have?
Where?
I don't know.
Today's word is Don Guri no Seikurabe.
Don Guri no Seikurabe.
Yes, yes.
Donguri has the same height.
Well, it's used when there's no difference between the two.
Well then, today as well, donguri, korokoro, okiraku, gokuraku!
Donkuri, korokoro, okiroku, gokuroku!
Well done!
Who is it?
Yes!
Commander!
I'm coming with you!
To-no-ha-gu-bu-ta-gu!
When your lips are dry, it's good to apply honey.
Set, go!
Hi, Aeon.
I came again this week.
You didn't take any of my requests.
Since then, I've been thinking about it day and night.
Look, I've made so many bears.
Do you know what a bear is?
It's not like there's a bear hanging under your eyes.
No, it's not.
There's a black line like this.
Good job!
Alright!
You're looking good today!
I've got a lot of work to do!
That's right!
Today's guest is a kitchen artist.
I am a kitchen artist.
He looks like a cook, but his job is not to cook.
This is his work tool.
His job is to make various things from the styrofoam.
To cut it well, you need this hand-made cutter.
It's hard to cut a wrinkled part.
But the kitchen artist can easily cut such a part.
Great job!
Use this knife to carve out the details like a sculpture.
It's starting to take shape.
It's a big crab decoration.
Hey, good job!
This was all made from the steam roll.
Kitchen artist's work is in the restaurant and party venue.
to make a big ornament.
With what he has made, it will be fun to eat.
This is the job of a kitchen artist!
Amazing!
Let's start with Chibi.
It's Robot-kun's funny story!
No.
1.
Even if an elephant is an elephant, what is the elephant inside the body?
A dead elephant!
What?
Oh, you got it right away.
That's good.
Oh, but there's a lot of things like a little knee, right?
Then this question was a bad question.
That's not true.
Is it funny?
I got it!
You didn't get it, did you?
Is it funny?
Okay, now that we're all ready, let's go to the next one.
Okay!
Asano Bun-gaku Minamika Exhibition 4
One day, Miller met a cute girl with a little mysterious beauty at the usual store.
I'm Miller.
What's your name?
It's Mara.
I wanted to meet someone like you.
Will you come to my house?
The two became close friends and spent the night together.
You are very warm.
After that, Mira and Mara spent the night together many times.
Milan is in the same bed as Mara, and it makes me feel so happy that my heart is pounding and I can fly up in the sky.
A day of a righteous ally.
In the afternoon, a monster settles down.
What kind of pencil do girls hate?
Pencils girls hate?
Um... Pencil?
I don't know.
What is it?
The answer is a pencil.
Ah!
Good morning.
Mr. Junko Miyokawa.
Let's make it with flowers!
Let's decorate the cake with flowers today.
Flower cake!
I think it's very cute to decorate it with a cake for your birthday or Christmas.
The ingredients are flowers, toothpicks, and aluminum foil.
Aluminum foil, toothpicks, and flowers.
First, leave a little bit of the stem and cut it.
Put a toothpick on the stem.
Let's wrap it with aluminum foil Wrap it with aluminum foil
Here are some flowers.
Then, place the flowers side by side on the cake.
Place the flowers side by side.
If you use a small flower, you can draw a letter on top of the cake.
I think it's cute to put water in a bowl and let the flowers float.
Nice.
I'm doing pretty good today, right?
Yeah!
I was always losing confidence because I was always showing my lower body.
That's right.
It's good to go like this.
This time...
But it's not good to have a lot of answers.
What?
I've got a lot of questions with answers this time, so this mystery is also an angel with sweet nails.
Did you get it?
I have no idea.
When I don't get it, it gets messy.
Well, I'm going to go to bed.
I'm so tired that I can't sleep.
See you later!
Bye-bye!
She's dancing with a ball in her skin.
Ugaa Ugaa Ugaa Ugaa
Who are you?
Yes, I am Ojiizo.
What did you think of today's mystery-telling, Robot-kun?
It was fun, wasn't it?
Yes, yes.
Both of your mystery-telling was really good.
Teach me the correct Japanese for the reward.
Okay!
What do you say when you say, you can eat?
You can eat.
Or, you can eat.
I can eat it!
That's right, Orico Orico!
You can eat it!
You can definitely eat it!
Tabe-ra-re-ru.
Remember that.
Tabe-re-ru means hot pot or hot pot.
My mouth is dirty, so my mouth is clean.
That's right.
Well, that's good.
Bye!
At first, it's round and round
I'm sorry.
Eat your food and evolve