Good morning.
I'd like to be on TV, but I don't know about you.
That's right.
You look very colorful today.
Do you like it?
Yes.
Ugo-go, what do you think of Ryuga today?
I think it's good.
Well, if you ask me, I'd say it's poisonous.
You don't know that, do you?
That's right.
To have poison and to control it.
Can you say it?
Doku wo omo desu.
Good, good.
Well done.
That's all for today.
Have fun.
Have fun!
Who is it?
Cheers!
It's shrimp!
Oto no Hakubutsu-tan!
Don't make so much noise You shouldn't Oh, I wouldn't Well, you must And I won't As long as we've got that clear
Nice to meet you.
I'm Shure.
I have a question.
I'm always confused which one to choose.
For example,
Which do you like more, dancing or dancing?
Why do you like dancing?
I don't know.
Please dance.
Great.
Very good.
Can you dance?
Let's move on to the next question.
Which do you prefer, fish or meat?
Why?
You don't like meat?
Because fish are nutritious.
Meat is nutritious.
I like meat.
Do you eat meat?
Yes.
Are you on a diet?
I'm on a diet too.
So, the question is...
The question is... Is it possible to eat only a little of delicious food?
Which do you prefer, bad or disgusting?
Disgusting!
Hurry up and decide.
It's good.
A little bit of good food?
What are you going to do?
Why?
Because... Let's move on to the next question.
Is that okay?
Yo!
Tell us!
Great people Good morning Great people of the universe, Professor Kazuhiko Sato of Tokyo University
Today, I would like to talk about the size of the universe.
The size of the universe.
Have you ever seen a beach on a summer night?
In fact, the Amano River is a collection of the stars.
In fact, the Amano River is a collection of stars, including our sun.
This is what we call the galaxy of the Milky Way.
The size of the galaxy of the Milky Way, where the stars gather,
It goes from end to end, and it takes 100,000 years for it to shine.
So it's about 100,000 light-years away.
How big is the universe as a whole?
Let's take this galaxy and cut it with a pencil.
Let's say there's a dot on the paper.
Let's say the dot is the size of a galaxy.
Then the space is the size of...
It's as big as the Tokyo Dome.
That's how big it is.
Of course, we don't know if the universe is still expanding beyond the Tokyo Dome.
But now we know that there is a universe up to that level.
Oh, oh, oh.
Asano Bun-gaku Japanese, Part 2
Puruso, who escaped from his mother's funeral, came to the beach.
Ah, the ocean feels so good.
A cute girl came to the place where Ursou was swimming.
I'm Marie.
The two got along quickly.
Will you marry me?
But Murusawa didn't like Marie at all.
To be continued...
Drawing and singing.
Which one do you like?
Eh?
Which one do you like, Ruka?
Drawing and singing.
Singing?
Yes, singing.
Drawing!
You don't like pigs?
I don't like pigs.
You don't sing with them?
Pigs.
What do you think?
I like to sing.
Really?
Don't you sing with me?
One, two, three, four.
I got it.
Let's move on to the next question.
Yes, please line up.
The last question.
Is it a boy or a girl?
Please say it quickly.
It's a girl!
Thank you.
Is this a secret?
See you next week.
Bye!
I have a lot of work to do!
My job is to cut her hair clean.
I also clean her ears.
It is also the job of a trimmer to cut the nails neatly.
Cute pets They are the customers of Trimmer
Trimmer's work is being carried out in such a pet shop where they live.
The trick to prevent pets from rampaging is to talk to them gently Then, as you can see, they will relax
She's getting closer to the beauty again Next is shampoo Don't forget to talk to her here
It's so cold.
After shampooing, of course, dry it with a dryer.
She's a good girl.
If you bring your face to your chest,
I can hear the sound of a human heart.
That makes me feel at ease.
It's time to cut The barricade she is using is excellent for drying human hair
If you do this, any place will be dry as you can see.
This place will be dry as well.
The last step is to cut it using scissors.
And it's done See, it shrunk so much that it can be replaced
This is the job of a trimmer.
Well done!
It's a wonderful job.
I like dogs and cats.
I want them to aim for the top.
If you sleep on the road, you'll get hit by a car!
Wheeze.
Dingus.
Chichi and Kaka At first they are round and round
Chichi-ka-ka, chichi-ka-ka, chika-chika-chin
Futago no chichi to kaka shippo ga tore
Eat food and evolve