Good morning.
Thank you for the warm greeting.
Today's phrase is, Good morning.
Good morning.
You don't need this.
Say, good morning.
Good morning.
Do you know why they say good morning in the morning?
Because it's morning.
What about Ugo?
Good morning is the beginning of praising each other for waking up early.
It's nice to be praised in the morning, isn't it?
Yes!
So, I hope you all have a happy morning, and I hope you keep saying good morning in a loud voice.
Is that okay?
Well, then, have a good rest of the day.
Have a good rest of the day!
Yes, well done.
Tasmania Devil!
How's that?
Good morning.
I'm going to eat green iguana today.
Green iguana!
I'm going to eat green iguana with jam.
The maximum height is about 1.8 meters.
We mainly eat fish and vegetables.
If you buy it, prepare a 60cm tank.
A 60cm tank.
I live in a place with a lot of wind, so I need a heater.
I set it to about 25 degrees.
Also, you need a place where you can walk in the sun.
Please bring a light bulb there.
I like water, so I need a place like that.
I live in the jungle, so I need a place with trees.
The vegetables are cabbage and pumpkin.
There are also fruits and bananas.
If you get used to it, you can buy it as a gift in Canada.
Please try it.
Thank you for watching!
Okay.
Good morning.
You're always so cute.
Thank you.
In French, it's merci.
Merci.
It's quite similar.
Now, Shuru-kun's French lesson.
In Japanese...
What's that?
In French, it's a keskuse.
Ketsukuse.
Not Ketsukuse.
Kesskuse.
Okay, put your right hand out.
And your index finger.
What is it?
It's pretty good.
Well, if you wrap a disposable回廊 in a lunch box, it will become a special lunch box.
Subtitles by SteamTeam
Do you want to get 100 points in the test or win the first prize in the relay?
Which do you prefer?
I got 100 points in the test.
What about you, Ugo?
I got a relay.
Why?
Because my legs get faster.
Have you ever won the first prize with a relay?
I've never been in third place.
I see.
That's pretty good.
Ryuga-chan, why did you get 100 points in the test?
It's important.
I want to praise my mom.
I see.
That wasn't pork cutlet?
Ruga, have you ever gotten a perfect score in a test?
But now, there's only one.
I have a lot of work to do!
That's right!
My job is an animal health technician.
My job is to take care of dogs and cats at the animal hospital.
I am an animal health technician.
Even healthy dogs sometimes get sick.
In that case, take them to an animal hospital.
Animal Health Technician's job is to help the doctor at the animal hospital.
If the dog goes wild, you can't check it, so you have to hold it gently to make it easier to check.
I'm going to hold the dog.
The dog is also nervous in front of the doctor.
The dog hates to be examined.
But the Animal Health technician is by his side, so the dog is relieved.
The inspection is over in no time!
Well done!
A dog with a serious illness will be hospitalized.
Animal health technician will take care of the dog so as not to make the dog lonely.
Depending on the dog's illness, they measure their body temperature and give them medicine.
The dog who doesn't like medicine, look!
He drank it!
It's okay if it's slimy.
Yes!
Well done!
The dog is so energetic that he can even yawn!
This is the job of the Animal Health Foundation!
I want to be a dog!
Morning Literature!
Howdy Saku!
Test 3!
Tess, who was about to forget about the sad event, decided to work in the farm this time.
Every day at the farm surrounded by the peaceful nature has healed my broken heart little by little.
She was about to fall in love with Claire, the son of a boxer.
And on the night of the wedding, Tess told everyone about her misfortune.
Then Correa suddenly got angry and left her and went to Brazil alone.
It's time to decide.
I'm thinking of something new.
Thank you very much.
Listen carefully.
The question is, which do you think is more important, the faculty or the students?
Elitchin.
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
What is Elitchin?
Eri-chin is a Russian word... Oh, sorry.
Eri-chin...
Sorry, I'll do it again.
Eri-chin is the president of the Russian Republic.
I chose that one.
President.
What about Gakyuin?
Gakyuin.
Ruga-chan is a great person.
But he's also a great student.
Uogogo-kun, have you ever been a student?
No!
I've been doing this since I was in fifth grade.
Shure-kun!
Yes?
You're great!
You're my king!
You're the best!
I see.
It's a life-threatening episode.
La question.
A date with Nagisa Oshima or a date with Nagisa Oshima?
Which is better?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Hmm...
One day of a runner.
Even if you eat a lot, you can't take it.
Wow!
Ugo Ugo Luger Fever!
Mikau Seijin appears.
Hola!
UNAGI NO KIMOTO DONNA TOKI MO
Shiro-kun is really persistent.
But there are people who are really looking forward to this.
Well then, here you go.
No matter what, no matter what...
This is the violin part.
Every time, every time, whenever I become who I am,
I want to hold on to the feeling of liking what I like.
It's wonderful.
Shura!
Which do you like more, Tokimo or Eton Maki Maki?
That's a hard one.
Let's go!
How about you, Tajima?
How about you, Buoko?
I said my real name.
Let's sing together.
3, 2, 1, go!
Maki maki tomaki maki Hite hite ton ton ton
It was pretty fun.
Now, I'm going to go back to France.
See you!
Ciao!
Bye-bye!
A date in the fall!
Abe-kun, who is on a date, is trying to set a trap!
You're going to get punched in the back!
Who are you?
I'm the late, late, late, late, late...
Lastly, I'll teach you the words you need to say on TV.
Thank you.
Listen twice.
ICHIDO MONO IE.
ICHIDO KIITE.
ICHIDO MONO IRE.
Not MONO IRE, but MONO IE.
MONO IRE.
Monoie.
Monoie means to listen to other people's stories.
Yes!
This is pretty hard, but let's practice.
So, see you later!
Bye-bye!
Me ga dete kita yo
Chichi Kaka Chichi Kaka Chichi Kaka Chichi Kaka Chichi Kaka Chichi Kaka Chika Chika Ching
Futago no chichi to saka shippo ga tore
Eat rice and evolve as an amateur