Hey, Ugo Ugo
Today you two look like a festival.
I want to see Ruga-chan's face again.
What's that on your cheek?
Did you paint it red?
What is it?
It's my dad's...
I copied his cheeks.
I copied it, so it looks good on you.
By the way, don't tell your wife about the autumn eggplant.
Do you know?
I don't know.
What do you know?
Aki-nasu.
Aki-nasu?
Don't tell your wife.
I don't understand.
I don't understand the meaning.
That's life, that's life.
Okiraku gokuraku.
Who are you?
I'm Jace Sato.
Koto no Hakubu-san!
To East of Lugas!
Tosa no ma, tosa no ma, tosa no ma, ha!
Aya!
Appare, appare!
I'm glad I didn't make a mistake.
How many of these numbers are there?
Is the number of Ugo Ugo strong?
Numbers?
It's math.
Yeah, it's strong.
Then I'll give you a hard one.
Okay, give it to me.
Supermarkets, well, I didn't have one myself, but in convenience stores,
It's a shopping cart made of plastic, but do you know how much it costs?
It's pretty expensive, isn't it?
It's not expensive.
It's just 9 yen.
1.
How many lugs do you think Luger has?
Have you ever gone shopping?
Never.
Of course not.
The correct answer is 500 yen.
It's a big deal.
What do you think?
Good morning.
Professor Katsuhiko Sato of Tokyo University.
Today, I would like to talk about what will happen to the universe.
What will happen to the universe?
Now we know that the universe is expanding like a balloon.
Will it continue to spread and expand?
Will it start to shrink this time?
Just like when the air is released from the balloon.
Actually, we don't know which one it is yet.
However, we can see how fast the universe is expanding.
If you can do this properly, you can do this.
is the right thing to do.
But if the universe starts to shrink in the future,
This is a long, long, long time ago.
So now...
There is no need to worry about the shrinking of the universe.
Asano Bungaku!
The Final Episode of the Illegal People!
Murusou got used to living alone in the prison.
Even though he was about to be executed, he was excited as if he was waiting for his birthday.
I'm looking forward to it.
I hope the day of execution doesn't come soon.
Mursong looked at the shining stars from the window of the prison and felt very happy.
The end.
Bread, bread, but I can't eat bread.
It's bread.
It's totally different.
Is it different?
It was good.
It's a frying pan, right?
That's right.
As expected of the lord.
No, it's not.
What is it?
It's a panda.
I can't eat pandas, but I can answer both.
I said both, so it's my win.
Shut up!
Don't talk there!
You're kidding!
Hozake is my specialty.
I'm tired, so I'm going to change it.
Can I change it?
No.
Tosa no ma Tosa no ma Tosa no ma
That's it for now.
Goodbye!
Not yet.
Not yet, right?
You can go home.
No!
See you next time!
Good luck, good luck.
It's hard to go home.
Bye bye.
Oshigataippai!
I was born and raised in Kasa, and I love making umbrellas.
This is an old Japanese umbrella.
It's called wagasa.
It's made of paper and bamboo sticks.
Negishi Nenosuke has been making wagasa since he was 15.
What he makes is very different from the one you use He makes it by cutting bamboo
Then, they are cut with a saw.
And then divide it into two parts.
And then the umbrella is assembled.
This is his work tool.
Once the umbrella is assembled, the paper is put on it.
This is a special mold called washi.
Each piece is carefully pasted with glue.
It's strange to say this myself, but I have a bad temper.
I'm the type of person who wants to do what others don't want to do.
I'm really into Mugara right now.
Wagasa craftsmen who protect Japanese tradition never give up until the last piece is pasted.
He checks the condition of the finished umbrella one by one.
This is the job of an umbrella maker.
Well done!
I think it's the most fun to go all the way to the finish line.
Every craftsman has learned this.
When I was in the front line...
Juiz de Burgos!
Who are you?
It's me, the fortune teller.
I'll see you in a minute.
Bye bye!
It's round in the first place.
Roll, roll, roll, roll
Take a bath and evolve Your tail will grow
Me ga dete kita yo
Kutanbo no chichi to kaka shippo nara
Eat your food and evolve!