Hoho, it's a good morning again today.
The TV seems to be in a good mood, so I'd like to laugh, but how about the three of us try laughing?
No!
Would you like to try laughing?
Ready, set, go!
Today's word is...
Laugh!
If you live a happy life, you will be happy.
Today, let's have fun and laugh together.
Have fun!
Who are you?
Good morning.
I'm a high school girl.
How are you?
To-to-to-to-to-to
What's up, sir?
Hey, I heard that a glass of water in the morning will make your poop come out better.
Ready, set, go!
Last week, it was a chicken, but today we are reborn.
Moshinobu Dadabuhi!
Did you get it, you two?
I got it!
Alright!
Lots of work to do!
That's right!
Today's work is a gyoza craftsman.
My job is to make gyoza.
I'm a gyoza craftsman.
This is a gyoza.
To make delicious gyoza, the skin of the gyoza is important.
He's cutting one dumpling now.
He's using a fork to make it round.
Gyoza craftsmen are very skillful.
No matter how many they make, they are all the same size.
Excellent!
This is the inside of the dumpling.
Gyoza craftsmen can make various kinds of gyoza, such as vegetables, meat, and shrimp.
No matter how fast you are, it won't stick out.
If you are a gyoza craftsman, you can make a flower-shaped gyoza.
The gyoza craftsman knows how to wrap the skin of the gyoza.
Great!
This is Ryoza's job.
Amazing!
If Luga-chan kisses you, what are you going to do?
That's weird.
What should we do?
Ruga-chan said it's fine.
It's fine?
Ruga-chan, do you want to go?
No, I don't want to.
Ruga-chan, why don't you go?
Good day.
Good day?
Why?
Good.
Really?
Asano Bun-gaku!
Minami Kaikisen, the third episode!
Eventually, Miller started working at a New York telecom company.
But people at the same workplace didn't like him at all.
However, there was only one thing I was looking forward to in the future.
It was to write a novel about how people at the same workplace failed and were scolded.
Okay, now I'm going to draw the part where he gets mad at me.
Here I go!
A day on the side of justice.
Lunch.
It's good!
Kame-Ginba!
If the school is gone, what will you two do all day?
I'm playing.
Playing?
What are you playing?
Chirin.
Shiritori.
Ho, ho, ho.
I want to play outside.
What do you want to play outside?
Nawa-tobi.
Nawa-tobi, huh?
What about you, Ugo-go?
I'll study at home.
What's wrong with her?
She'll be in trouble if she loses her school.
Because if I become a father, if I don't study enough, I can't be a father.
Oh, that's interesting.
Yo!
Good morning.
Today, let's make a simple bouquet.
What you need is a flower, a string, and a ribbon.
First, cut each flower into the same stem length.
If there is a leaf in the center of the flower stem, please remove it.
Remove the leaf.
First, take a flower and add another flower around it.
At this time, try not to line up the same flowers as much as possible.
You can make a cute bouquet if you make the big flowers low and the small flowers a little higher.
Lower the large flower and raise the small flower.
Once you have a bouquet of flowers with all the flowers, tie it with a string and tie it.
Tie the middle with a string.
I'm going to put a ribbon on this string, but if it's a normal ribbon knot, it won't be able to take a pretty shape.
In this case, first attach a knot to the string with a ribbon.
And make two rings with another ribbon.
Let's tie this other ribbon with the first ribbon.
You can also make a large bouquet in this way.
What if there's no more rice in this world?
What if it's just bread?
That's fine.
Is that fine?
No!
No?
You don't like it?
No.
Why is that, Ugo Ugo-kun?
It's me, right?
I don't like it either.
Wow, it's like a YouTube channel.
But the food is...
I can't hear you.
But the food...
All you have to do is have food.
Wow, that's great.
What do you think, Gogo-kun?
I'm going to run a restaurant.
You're running a restaurant?
I can't do it without rice.
I can't eat without rice.
I see, so the conclusion is that you can't live without it?
That's right!
Speaking of food, I'm a little hungry.
I'm going home soon.
Let's meet again next week!
Yeah!
See you!
Bye bye!
When I was training in the straight end, I got hit by Senna.
I'm an alien, puang puang puang puang puang
Did you like today's video?
Yes, I did.
Was it fun?
Yes.
Let me tell you the truth.
This is the correct Japanese for TV.
How do you count the white squids in the sea?
What?
How do you count a squid?
One?
What?
One.
Correct.
One times two.
Just like the juice in the cup, you have to count one and two.
Okay.
Did you get it?
Yes!
Then let's count a few more days today.
See you later!
Bye-bye!
Thank you for watching
Go!
Chichi Kaka, Chichi Kaka, Chichi Kaka.
Chichi Kaka, Chichi Kaka, Chichi Kachi.
The father of the twins and Takashi Porado
Eat rice and evolve.