We do control.
It's morning.
Are you both hungry?
Hungry.
Hungry?
If there's cake and daifuku here,
What will you do?
Cake!
What about you, Ugo-go?
I love cake!
Then I'll tell you what I'm going to say today.
Okay.
Those who follow the will never follow the will.
What?
The cake and the... Say it again.
The two big things don't make one big thing.
Nitto!
Koumono!
Nitto omoezu.
I don't think so.
If you're too greedy to eat cake and daifuku, you'll get a stomachache and won't be able to eat either.
Do you remember?
Yes.
Well, today, we had a good time.
We had a good time.
Well done.
Kero kero kaede desu!
Koto no Hakubu-san!
You know what?
Yo!
I heard it's good to drink warm milk when you can't sleep.
Here we go!
Uwogoruga!
I'm in trouble.
I was invited to a date.
What should I do?
It's too early.
I wonder?
It's a good song, isn't it?
I'm getting nervous.
My theme song.
Do you remember?
Yes!
Do you want to sing and be moved?
Do you want to?
Then, I'll sing a special song for you.
It's okay to sing.
3, 2, 1.
You're about to cry, aren't you?
Today's job is a nail artist.
My job is a nail artist.
I take care of my hands and feet, and help with the fashion of my nails.
Adults sometimes put makeup on their nails.
Long nails are thin and look beautiful.
The nail artist is the one who does the makeup as you like.
It's important to put your hands in front of the makeup.
The nail artist will peel off the thin skin of the nail to make it easier to put on makeup.
Use special scissors to carefully peel it off.
It doesn't hurt at all.
Put makeup nails on the real nails.
Nail artist paints magic clay with special powder on nails.
When the magic clay hardens, as you can see, real long nails are made.
Wonderful!
Let's ask the nail artist to show us his special skill He will make a hole in the nail and paint it with red paint
If you put the real diamond in the nail hole, the nail will look rich.
This is the job of a male artist
In front of the man I like, in front of the man I like, in front of the man I like, in front of the man I like, in front of the man I like, in front of the man I like, in front of the man I like,
This is so weird!
Super weird!
So weird!
I'm gonna get hated!
I can do it!
It's sad.
But, you know, my face is a little big.
I can't help it.
You...
Do you think so?
Yes!
I knew it!
Then I have no choice but to do my best even if I have to endure it!
Asano Bun-gaku Minami Kaikisen Daikai
In a town called Brooklyn, there was a child of a poor tailor.
His name was Henry Miller.
Miller was a poor boy who had never been loved by his mother.
So he always wanted to be loved by someone.
One day, Miller decided to give courage to a girl he fell in love with for the first time in his life.
Oh, I like you.
Please go out with me.
I don't want to.
Pillar's first love ended with a one-sided love.
Next!
A day on the side of justice.
In the morning, the neighborhood patrol continues.
It's a very embarrassing worry.
It's embarrassing to be asked by Kougo-kun.
How many times do I have to ask you?
Ugao-kun, can you cover your ears for me?
Yuga, will you listen to me?
Yes.
When I'm sleeping at night,
It seems that the seeds are blowing out from the inside of the body.
What do you think I should do to stop crying?
I'm tired.
Are you kidding?
Good morning.
Junko Kiyokawa!
Let's make flowers!
Let's make a bracelet with flowers today.
Flower Bracelet
We have ribbons, pochkis and flowers.
Ribbons, pochkis and flowers.
First, prepare a ribbon that is slightly longer than the length of your wrist.
Then, cut the stems of the flowers.
Put a flower on the ribbon and fasten it with a hotchkiss.
At this time, I think it's good to fasten it firmly in two places.
Stop with a hotchkiss.
When you stop a flower, the hotchkiss
At the base of the flower, hide the bottom of the flower and put the next flower on it.
Put the flowers on top of each other.
You can add some leaves between the flowers.
Repeat this for a long time.
And then...
At the end, leave the length of the ribbon to tie the ribbon.
If you make it longer, you can make a headdress or a neck ornament.
I'll bite your nose!
Kakuya?
If I bite your nose, won't you die?
I always put my nose in when I go to bed.
Really?
Don't cry, you'll be fine.
Yeah, but I'll die.
If you do that, you won't be able to come here from next week.
What's that?
I'm doing it.
Are you okay?
Can you forgive me?
Right.
I see.
I can live like this again today.
Well then, bye-bye!
Bye-bye!
When you're eating at the hairpin...
Uga Uga Uga Uga Uga
Who are you?
Hi!
I'm Kanemochi's son.
Are you all eating?
I wonder when they'll stop crying.
I don't know.
Today, I'm going to teach you Japanese, as a thank you for being with me today.
It's the correct Japanese.
Okay!
What do you say when you say, Father?
Father!
Oh, good job, good job.
Then, what do you say when you say, Father?
It's a reward.
Oh, that's great.
Ugo Ugo is very good at it.
Be careful when you use polite words.
Okay.
Have a great day!
Bye!
Me ga dete kita yo
Chichi Kaka, Chichi Kaka, Chichi Kaka Chichi Kaka, Chichi Kaka, Chichi Kachin
Futago no chichi to zaka Shippo naka
Eat your food and evolve