Good morning.
Today is Friday, the day of breakfast.
Before breakfast, let's say a few words.
Yes.
Okay?
Asameshimae.
Do you know it?
No, I don't.
Do you know it, Ryuga?
Asameshimae means something that can be done easily.
Did you get it?
Yes!
Asameshi is not a good word, but it's a good word to use.
Remember asameshimae.
Yes!
That's all for today.
Have fun!
Well done!
Kega-nin desu.
Oto no Hakubu-san!
It's time for breakfast.
Do you all remember your spells?
Yes, we do.
Go ahead.
Tak-shak!
Ran-ran-poo!
Yes, the TV is going first.
Welcome.
Please come in.
Itadakimasu.
Please eat.
Duck it.
Sesame has a lot of vitamin C, so your skin will be smooth.
Your skin will be more beautiful when you eat sesame seeds.
I like salmon.
Yes.
What kind of beans are these?
These are Japanese beans.
Greenpeace's Wafu Potage Soup And Greenpeace!
Greenpeace and...
I know that Greenpeace hates children on TV, so I made it into soup.
This is Greenpeace.
I always eat it.
Do you eat it?
How about you, Ryuga?
I like this flavor.
I'll sit.
If you think you caught a cold, you should go to bed right away.
Thank you very much.
Don't talk to each other.
Tell the TV.
No, everyone will know.
Tell them.
I made a lot of rice, so I'll teach you how to make it.
It's so good!
I'm so surprised.
Ugo Ugo is hungry now.
Are you two satisfied?
Yes!
What about you?
We are satisfied!
Do you remember the spell to go back to your room?
Yes, I do.
Say it.
Yes, I'll go back to my room first.
Puku puku nan puku nan puku pu!
Guppy, taboo, taboo!
Boo-hee!
Boosh, boosh, boosh, boosh!
Boo-hyo!
Ya-ho!
You guys had breakfast again, didn't you?
Yeah!
This is so unfair!
I'm starving.
Huh?
You're all dressed up weird!
Ugo Ugo-kun and Luga-chan?
Yeah!
Huh?
We've got a lot of work to do!
That's right!
Today's work is by Narrator Companion.
My job is to introduce and explain products at events and exhibitions.
I am a narrator companion.
When a new product is made, an event is held to show it to everyone.
All the products are still unknown to everyone, so it's a little difficult just to watch.
I have no idea.
Narrator Companion can explain how to use the products here easily to anyone.
It's very difficult to explain the new product No matter how long the explanation is, the narrator companion will be able to memorize it
He is very good at speaking So everyone is listening to him Well done
Narrator Companion has thin legs and long hair.
He looks like an idol.
The way he holds the microphone is perfect.
If you speak with a microphone like this, the sound won't leak to the surroundings, so the voice of the familiar companion will be heard as it is.
Look!
More and more people are coming!
Great!
This is the job of a narrator-companion!
Amazing!
Morning Literature!
Hardy Saku Test Introduction!
Clare, who had been waiting for a long time, has finally returned to Tess, who had been living in Alec's mansion.
Don't look at Clare's face.
I thought I was going to kill Alec.
What?
Why?
The two of them ran away from the mansion.
Don't ever come to me alone again.
Tess was happy to be born in such a fun time.
Soon after, she was arrested by the police and arrested.
What if they eat too much food and get bigger and bigger?
If it gets as big as Godzilla...
What are you going to do?
I'm going to work out hard.
Work out?
I...
I'm going to scare people!
How?
Scream!
Can you really enjoy it?
Can you enjoy it?
Poor thing, isn't she?
Poor thing?
Who?
When she was walking,
What will you do if you destroy the company?
I thought it was a good time.
That's right.
We'll see you next time!
Is there anything you want to do as an adult?
Yes!
No!
R-Ruga-chan, what do you do?
I'm an actress!
An actress?
What does an actress do?
Here's a question!
Don't you always say that you're an actress?
Because I really want to be one.
Stop it, you two.
Why?
What are you doing?
What did I just say?
What did you say?
No.
What?
Actress?
Why do you have to be an adult to become an actress?
One day, a runner...
At night, they practice even in their dreams.
The family is not satisfied.
The End.
Wow!
Uro, Uro, Uya!
Ah, God!
Kawaii!
Mikan Seijin is here.
Mwah!
That's enough!
Latte-ssu!
It comes out of the nose like this.
See you next week.
Next time, I'm going to make a mushroom that even you know.
Mr.
Pig.
What?
Next time, make sure you eat properly.
All right, then.
I hope you don't fall.
And don't let your nose bleed.
But, but, I'm so excited.
If I get in trouble, I'll come out.
I got it.
Then I'll make a tissue and put it in your nose.
I'll give it a try.
I'll give it a try next time!
Okay!
I think you should give it a try.
Thank you.
Thank you for the advice.
Well then, see you next week!
Bye-bye!
An autumn date!
I'm going to take a picture of Abe-kun on the bench.
You're going to get beaten up!
Kegani desu!
Saikin kei haete kimashita!
Now, let's play a game from the TV.
Okay.
If you catch a cold on the TV, what will you give to the visitor?
A bouquet of flowers!
You are.
What do you want, Ryuga?
I got it.
What is it?
A toy.
A toy?
What kind of toy?
A car.
I can't wait.
But don't catch a cold.
You two will be fine today.
Bye-bye.
Me ga dete kita yo
Chichi Kaka, Chichi Kaka, Chichi Kaka.
Chichi Kaka, Chichi Kaka, Chichi Kachin.
Futago no chichi to kaka shippo ga tore
Watch the next one, too!