Good morning.
Are you planning to start something new this year?
What are you going to do?
I'm going to clean the house.
It's been a long time since you started cleaning.
Hajime ga daiji.
Hajime ni shita koto ga zutto wari made eikyou suru no te nani wo suru ni mo
Let's think about it carefully before we do it.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Then, today, too, let's have fun and have fun!
Let's have fun and have fun!
Thank you for watching!
Who are you?
I'm the president.
I don't have money.
Trust me.
Good morning, everyone.
Let's make delicious yakisoba with everyone today.
How to make Kanto-style Yakisoba
The ingredients are steamed rice, bean sprouts, char siu, shrimp, and so on.
Steamed noodles, bean sprouts, fried shrimp, and shrimp.
First, fry the bean sprouts for a while.
Then, put it in a bucket and drain the water.
Fry the bean sprouts and cut them into slices.
Then, heat the frying pan well.
Add char siu, bean sprouts, soba, and other ingredients.
Add them all at once and stir-fry well.
The seasoning is salt, pepper and soy sauce.
The point here is oyster sauce.
It's the oil from the catty.
If you add a bit of it, it'll be even better.
It'll be even better.
Add oyster sauce.
This is Cantonese-style yakisoba.
If you find it difficult to use fire, ask your mother.
Mikan Seijin appears.
Ken-dama!
Happy New Year!
Since it's a new year, I'd like to tell you two something.
Up until last year, I was kind of weak-willed.
I always listened to their facial expressions.
It was a bad robot, wasn't it?
That's how it breaks.
That's right.
It breaks right away.
But from this year onwards, I'll always be proud of myself.
I'll always be strong and brave.
I'm thinking of becoming a Terminator-like robot.
Terminator!
Right?
Do I look strong?
You're weak!
Happy New Year.
If your friend asks how much you got from your friend, you should give him a small amount.
Hello, Hugo Hugo Luga is very happy to wish you a great year.
Goodbye.
It's been an hour since Daisaku and the others met.
There is a young man.
He is a young man who admires Nankishin and photographer Shinoyama Kishin.
What's wrong, Asuka?
I'm busy, so please go home.
I'll go home then.
Not you.
As soon as they got in, they started talking.
There's no one, Yumi.
I'm sorry, but you're a great person to eat all the tonkatsu in the store by yourself.
Daishaku was praised as a great man, and he hugged him and kissed him many times.
I'll leave it to the police.
Wait a minute.
I'll replace the amount he ate with this number.
Who is this woman who suddenly appeared?
And what will happen to Daisaku?
The mystery calls the mystery and continues in the next episode.
Now it's time to play with the robot.
This year, the order has changed.
Today, we're going to do something like a festival.
That's right.
It's a good year.
Let's go!
I drew 20 pictures in the morning.
I see.
How many did you draw in the afternoon?
I don't know how to do it.
I'm tired, so I'll do 10.
That's not it.
I don't know how to do it.
This is it.
7 pieces.
Huh?
Why?
I don't know.
The two of us.
5 x 5 is 25.
25 pieces.
That's what I'm saying.
Morning Literature!
Red and Black, Episode 4
It can't be helped because it's a cute daughter's wish.
Ramor, who allowed Mathilde and Julian to get married, even gave him a great job as a guard.
But immediately after that, a letter from Lady Renard, who had written about Julian, was delivered to the Duke, and the dream of Julian's birth disappeared.
When he returned to his hometown, he fired a pistol at Lady Renard, who was praying in the church, and was arrested on the spot.
I learned how to draw fish.
What kind of fish is that?
It's the sound of a fart.
I'm not going to teach you.
Fart.
This is the hint.
I'm going to fart.
What?
I don't know.
Boo Boo Boo!
Eh, eh, bu?
Bu?
Buta?
That's not it.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
No more.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12...
The answer is... What?
You're not the one who said it.
I'm sorry.
No way!
Robot-kun is coming.
Robot-kun is so excited today.
When I turned around, he stood up.
I'm sorry.
I was too nervous.
I'll do it one more time.
If you turn around, you'll stand up, but if you stop, you'll fall asleep.
I got it!
My heart!
Luka?
Yes, Luka-chan.
Why?
What's the reason?
I got it!
It's because of my father.
Your father?
I got it!
Koma!
Correct!
I thought you knew.
Did I say something weird?
You know, when you do this,
It doesn't make any sense.
It's not connected, is it?
On the same day,
He went too far and got scolded.
Happy New Year, Ugo Ugo Luka.
Ugo!
One, two, three.
Ugo, Ugo, Lugo!
Happy New Year!
Hooray!
Boom, boom, achi gato boom Oike no mawari ni nobara ga seetayo Boom, boom, boom, achi gato boom
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Good luck this year, Masao!
Hey.
Yeah.
What do you eat when you get on a boat?
I won't give you a hint.
A mochi!
A bird!
Let's just say what we think.
Anyway, I'm in a good mood for the new year, so I'll be in your care from now on.
Yes!
Well then, bye bye!
Bye bye!
It's the beginning of the new year!
We're going to be blown away to France!
Who are you?
Shabu-shabu-shabu-shabu-shabu...
It's related to Hajime, okay?
Yes.
Hajimehanbun.
That's right.
It doesn't mean anything at all.
Please don't do anything like that.
That's what I thought.
Everything depends on how you do it at first.
If you do it well, you'll be able to do half of it.
Let's do our best in the new year.
Yes.
See you later!
Bye-bye!