you
Good morning.
March is finally over.
Let's start with today's phrase.
Nishin-geppo.
It means that the world is progressing day by day.
This show, Go!
Go!
Luger, and Shingen, let's keep moving forward!
Yes!
Have a good day!
Yes, good job!
Oya-jibushi!
Go, go, Luka!
We're moving at the last minute!
Dad!
Oh, my God!
Well, today, I'm going to repeat the Kansai dialect I've taught you, okay?
Okay!
Let's start with a simple one.
How do you say thank you in Kansai dialect?
Oukini.
That's right.
Say Oukini.
Oukini.
That's pretty good.
The next one is a very important word.
It's used when someone asks you, are you making a profit?
Bocchi bocchi denga.
Dengang.
Well, that's a close call.
Next.
Yes, sir.
Make yourself at home.
Don't worry about it.
I can't do it with you.
I'm glad to hear that.
My heart is beating so fast.
One day, the son of a rich man goes to school in the morning.
One day, a rich man's son
You can study elegantly in the morning
A day of a son with a lot of money Lunch, a rich lunch
A day with a son with a lot of money.
F1 exchange in the garden in the afternoon.
A day of a rich man's son
Before you go to bed, use the money to buy flowers.
The end.
Are you ready?
Yes!
Let's go!
Are you ready?
Yes!
I'm asking you to do me a favor.
Please do me a favor.
Say it again.
Yoroshuu-san-gomo.
That's it.
Yoroshuu-tanomo.
Ha-ha!
Well, it's like a snack, like a chakamashi roll.
Well, chakamasu.
Chakamasu.
It means, would you like some tea?
Would you like some tea?
I don't know how to explain it in Kansai dialect.
Come on, say it.
What do you want to say?
It's pretty scary.
There might be a scout, so be careful.
Immediately after they are born, they hatch.
To be continued.
A Life of a Hatch insect
It's the first time to get a shaku.
Next.
The life of a shaku-tori-mushi.
Dad, you can do it!
Good luck!
The life of a shakutorimushi.
Life is full of shakus.
It's over.
What's that?
Got it?
Then let's go and enjoy the world!
Okay!
That's right.
That's how you do it.
And from April, you have to do it more and more.
Okay?
More and more.
Especially next week, unlike Yatsuhashi, there will be a live broadcast.
Do you understand?
There will be no replay.
Right?
So, keep it tight.
Yes, sir!
I'm going home now.
Bye bye!
Daddy, I want to play with you!
Yes, daddy!
Boo!
Hello!
How are you?
I'm fine!
Today, it's not Nendo Zaiku, it's Nendo Matsu!
It's a special of Mr. Gamotto's NaZuNaZu!
One day, a snowman...
In the morning, the snowman wakes up and washes his face.
One snowman's day.
In the morning, the snowman is sent by his family to get the prey.
To be continued.
A snowman's day.
He's there.
He takes a break and eats a little lunch.
To be continued
A Snowman's Day
5.
He was caught by a human and ran away in a hurry.
Next.
6.
A snowman's day.
Yogi was scolded by his wife for not taking the prey.
The end.
Question 1.
What is the sport that has a slope even if it is flat?
Even if you play where you can't enter, there is a slope.
Saka!
Next!
What is the animal that is always angry even though it has a kind face?
Gorilla!
Gorilla?
Um...
Elephant!
Elephant?
You know all the animals.
Chimpanzee!
Chimpanzee?
Luka-chan, how do you get angry when people get angry?
I get angry.
What do you say when you scream?
KUYA!
That's right.
You got it right!
I got it!
Rock, paper, scissors!
You're in good shape.
Ugo-kun, you're a little slow.
Boss bug!
Gogoruga!
I think I should take my pants off.
What is it that you want to throw away even though you bought it?
It's not like that.
I bought it, but I thought I'd throw it away.
It's like a sticker.
A sticker?
No, it's not.
It's something like that.
Gum tape.
Gum tape?
No, that's not it.
Something to throw away.
Ah, something like this.
I wonder if he knows.
I wonder if he doesn't know.
Wait a minute.
Koo-san?
He's smiling.
How is it?
Not yet.
Why not?
Not yet, not yet, not yet.
It's a sticky spring thing.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
Harumono .
.
TAPE!
One day, a wicked man.
In the morning, he buys milk from someone else's house.
The bad guy continues.
One day in the middle of a dark night.
The story of a bad cat who bullies a stray cat continues.
One day in the middle of the night.
He goes to the dining room to get a dish.
The bad guy continues.
One day, a very bad person.
A bad guy who doesn't let his old man take his seat.
Mm-hmm.
A day of a very bad person.
At night, a bad guy who puts today's bad news on his diary.
The end.
Eh?
What did you say?
Tape!
Tape?
Which country's specialty product is it?
A dolphin.
A dolphin?
Uguisse!
Uguisse?
Eh?
I don't know.
I think I forgot the problem.
I'll say it again.
I bought it, but I want to throw it away.
Well, I'm going to throw this away.
I'm going to throw this away.
Do you know the answer?
Anyone?
It's difficult.
Wait a minute.
I'll let you say it one more time.
What is it, Ryuga-chan?
A child.
Yes.
It's solidified.
One day in the life of a manzaishi.
He's been practicing bokeh and tsukkomi since this morning.
Yatterarumahen is a story of a manzaishi who can't sell.
In the morning, I had to run to the top of the gag.
I can't do it.
One day, a manzaishi couldn't make money, so he couldn't eat lunch.
A day of a non-selling manzaishi.
In the afternoon, the script for the gag is a mess after all.
I can't do special training.
A day of unsold manzai poems.
At night, as expected, I couldn't sleep at all.
Sayonara.
Kou-san?
Yes.
I'm frustrated.
I have an answer.
The answer is a sticker.
Huh?
Isn't it fun?
What's a sticker?
Oh, really?
You don't know?
I don't know!
Rocket Punch!
No!
1st year of elementary school.
Cherry blossom, cherry blossom, cherry blossom, cherry blossom, cherry blossom, cherry blossom
A year of brainwashing.
Summer.
Study outside.
Outside.
Continue.
One Year as an Elder
Nobunaga, Hideyoshi, Hiei, Asoga, Mine, Shirai, Tsutomi, Iijima, Ai, Hosokawa, Fumi...
They're in!
A year as a high school student.
He won a lottery in winter.
Daikyo.
Oh, Kamsa, please!
Alright, here we go!
Another spring.
No more.
My body is so hot.
Ah, Minami no Shima!
Minami no Shima.
Both are wrong.
Do you know what it means when you say that your body is hot?
Your body is hot.
Hotel!
Oh, that's good.
I know what it is.
What is it?
It's a game where you have to solve a puzzle.
A puzzle?
You have to solve the puzzle.
It was good that I got it right, right?
Anyway, I'm going home now.
I'll stop here for today.
It's not October, it's April, so let's be flexible and do our best.
Yes!
See you.
I'm going home.
Bye-bye.
In the spring, one of the foreign students said, I can't believe I'm eating such rotten food in the morning.
Japanese people don't understand at all.
One day, an international student was stuffed like a female cow in the morning.
I don't understand Japanese people at all.
One day, a foreign student.
It was noon.
This woman was a college student.
Japanese people don't understand at all.
One day, a foreign student said, I don't understand why there are so many Yankees.
One day, a foreign student
People in Japan don't know that they're doing ecchi on TV at night.
Next week will be a special live broadcast.
Right?
I don't know what's going to happen.
Let's do our best so that no one will say that we have a serious injury.
Please cheer for the people who are watching the TV.
Yes!
Then, let's have a great day today!
Bye-bye!