I don't have any words from the TV today.
Instead, I've taught you so far.
If you remember a word, please say it.
What does Ochanoko-saisai mean?
Here you go.
What about you, Luka?
I can see a smile on your face.
What does that mean?
You know, when you're embarrassed, your face turns red.
That's right.
Well done.
Let's learn a lot of new words from now on, okay?
Okay!
Let's do our best, Udonge-kun!
Yes!
Well then, today, let's have fun and have fun!
Let's have fun and have fun!
Yes, you did a good job.
Mikan Seijin appears.
Now I am, I am, I am...
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, let's start with the usual warming up.
Let's start with come on.
Come on!
Okay, and feel.
Fever.
And peas.
Okay!
But today, Tony will use the acting that he's learned from the two of them, and make them laugh and have them act.
Mikan Seijin appears.
We've been waiting for you.
The main event of the day.
RUO vs. RYUGA.
The winner of the comedy and acting battle.
Please give them a round of applause.
Please give him a big hand.
And the red corner, Uo-kun.
Let's move on to the first round.
First up is Luga-chan's Ah!
Laokisawa vs. Lugo-kun's father.
Okay?
Let's start with you, Ruka.
Start!
Okay, Roku-sama.
I did it.
That's all?
Oh, Roku-sama.
Oh, wait a minute.
Hello, Roku-sama.
Cabbage is cheap, isn't it?
Okay.
And Uo-kun's father, please.
Uo-kun's father, please.
Why don't we do it at the same time?
Okay?
Let's get excited and go for it!
Luka-chan versus Ugo-kun!
You're going to get pecked!
Lula-chan wins with courage.
Mikan Seijin has appeared.
Mwahahahaha!
Hoon-da-ra-da Hoon-da-ra Hoon-da-ra Hoon-da-ra Hoon-da-ra Hoon-da-ra Hoon-da-ra Hoon-da-ra Hoon-da-ra Hoon-da-ra Hoon-da-ra
Hon-da-ra-ra-ta, hon-da-ra-ga-da-ra-da, ho-yee-ho-da.
Now, the second round.
Luga-chan's big laugh vs. Uo-kun's cry.
Let's do this at the same time, okay?
Ready, start!
Oh, no!
Okay.
This is a draw.
The third round will decide the winner.
Ryuga wins.
And one more.
Good luck, Uo.
That's it.
Let's go.
The third round.
Luka's Gero Tai.
Ugo-kun's Hanage Nuki.
Let's get into it.
Wait a minute!
What's that, Ugo-kun?
Oh, you're a flower.
That's a good one.
Go into the flower as hard as you can.
Did you get it?
Are you ready?
Okay!
Ugo-chan's Gero vs. Ugo-kun's Hanage Nuki.
Let's get it started.
Ready, go!
And how about you, Luka?
Luka's Gero.
And Ugo's Hanaginuki.
I'm sorry, but Uo won because of his inferiority complex.
So it's a one-on-one win.
I love you!
Okay, and cry, oh mommy, oh mommy, oh mommy, oh mommy.
And then... And then... And then...
Are you a new girl?
Yes, I'm a new girl.
Sayuri, what's your name?
You remember me well.
And call me Mama.
Call Mama Taxi!
OK, and then laugh!
And then, Naoki-sama!
So, smile as much as you can at the end!
Okay, okay.
That's it!
Okay.
See you next week!
Bye-bye!
Duriana, Duriana, wow!
Thank you, thank you!
Don't believe in rumors.
My heart is a poop.
It's always a fun dream.
Good morning!
We've been working really hard for a long time.
Thank you for your hard work.
You're going to be lonely.
I don't want to!
Thank you for your hard work!
That's not true, right?
You can do it from now on, right?
Mikan Seijin.
Well then, the three of us have sung various songs so far, haven't we?
Yes.
Today, if we just sing a song, it won't sound like a children's show, so I want to go back to the origin and sing a song like a school song.
Thank you for watching!
Good idea!
Do you know the song KAKKO?
I do!
I don't know it.
I know it.
Ugo-kun, can you teach me?
It's similar!
Is it true?
Is it different?
The one about the quiet meal?
I don't know.
From the shadows of the forest
How do I look?
You don't know?
I was going to do this with the three of us.
I don't know.
Mikan Seijin is back.
I'm in trouble, Tomato.
I'm in trouble.
What should I do when I'm invited to a date?
I wonder if it's still too early.
I wonder if I should try this.
What do you mean?
So, when the person in front of you says, don't worry, the person next to you says, don't worry.
Oh.
Okay?
Then, what's the order?
Okay.
Then... What?
You go first?
After that.
After that?
Then, Ungo-ungo will be number one.
Tomato goes in the second hole and Ruga goes in the third hole.
Do you understand?
Don't get in trouble.
Don't get in trouble, don't get in trouble.
On a date, on a date, on a date.
I was invited, I was invited.
Let's try it!
Ready, set, go!
Don't get in my way!
Don't get in my way Don't get in my way
What should I do?
Is it still too early?
It's not over yet!
Now it's time for the next round.
Mikan Seijin appears.
Did it go well?
Yes, it did.
Then let's change the order.
Wait a minute!
What?
Then I'll teach you a new, true impression.
Do you understand?
For example, in this case, Ugongo-kun is always singing, saying, don't worry, invite me to a date.
And then, when Tomato said, "'Don't be in trouble'," Ugo Ugo-kun kept singing, saying, "'Don't be in trouble' again."
Ah, that...
I've heard of it somewhere.
Right?
Ah, it was in my class.
I did it in my class.
Then, let's practice what we did in the last lesson.
Okay.
Okay, this time it's Ruga-chan, Toma, and Ugogo-kun.
Ruga-chan will keep singing.
Okay.
Uwogawa-kun will sing the song, Tomato is in trouble.
Uwogawa-kun will sing the song.
Okay.
Okay, Ryouga-chan will start.
One, two, three!
Thank you!
One more time!
Let's do it again!
One, two, three!
It's Luka!
Don't get in trouble.
I don't know!
Mikau Seijin
Next time, Ruga will do it first.
Ruga, go ahead!
Wait a minute!
1, 2, 3!
I'm in trouble!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'll sing a song for you.
Okay, go ahead.
Wait!
Don't go on a date!
I did it!
I won!
Kamikaze Seijin Poyon!
See you later!
There's a school song called Kouka, right?
Can you sing it?
I can sing it, but...
I can only sing the middle part.
All right.
Ruga, you go first.
Go ahead.
One, two, three, four.
I want to go to elementary school.
That's great!
That's great.
Now it's Ugo-go's turn.
Let's go!
Yeah!
It's Ruka's debut!
That's it!
Gokushuu Shogakko!
Mikan Seiji, Dishonored
It's amazing.
Tomato sang too much last night, so she can't sing.
Ruka jumped off,
That's right.
I'm tired.
I went to the gym today.
But it was pretty fun.
I'm tired.
I might be happy to be here.
Oh.
Right.
Well then, let's continue to be good friends from now on, okay?
Okay!
Well then, ciao ciao and kai ciao!
Ciao ciao and kai ciao!
Bye bye!
Mikan Seijin, Mishuo.
Mikan Seiji, Mishuou
Go!
Lastly, I'll teach you a saying to tighten your heart.
Tuna no ue no ie Tuna no ue no ie
That's right.
The sand is slippery, so when you build a house, you fall right away.
In other words, a house on the sand means you don't know when you're going to fall.
Ugo Goryuga could be a house on top of the sand.
No!
No?
You might be right.
Let's keep our hearts tight and do our best.
Yes!
That's all for today.
We'll see you next time!
Bye-bye!