Okonomiyengei Theater.
Hideto Sanshotei and Yuka Shuncho perform live from the Fuji Theater.
Good morning.
Yesterday's live broadcast was a little reflective.
Let's do our best today on the third day.
Now, I'm going to go to your house.
Excuse me.
I'd like to say a few words to everyone watching the TV.
You may begin.
You can relax and be in a good mood.
This is a very important word, isn't it?
I hope you have a good time.
Okira-kun!
Kokura-kun!
Good job!
Good morning!
Today is the 3rd day.
I'm very tired.
Let's go right away.
Today's first entry.
Shure-kun will get angry.
If you suddenly like it, you can't throw it.
Don't get too excited.
Shuri, who was left to be an unfamiliar newscaster, made a lot of wrong comments yesterday.
The audience got angry with the person in charge.
Everyone, I'm sorry for the inconvenience.
I'm sorry for the inconvenience.
That's where the ceremony began.
Today's ceremony.
The total of 16 billion dollars is 5 yen, which is 11.5 billion yen.
It's a big difference.
$1.6 billion in Japanese yen and 1.8 billion yen in Japanese yen.
That's a lot.
Be careful not to fall down.
It's a great title.
Foreign Minister Fukusori Watanabe, who is a close friend of Michi, has been appointed as the Minister of Foreign Affairs yesterday.
Oh, that was close.
So, who's going to be the first one to come out?
Let's go next.
The next one is...
Yes, no, Clinton.
Yes, no, Piro.
Today is the 3rd day of President Clinton's presidency
Japanese people say NO when they say YES.
The U.S. Secretary of State admitted that there was such a statement.
Do you say hi and yeo properly?
You don't have to say hi no matter what you say.
Got it?
You don't understand at all, do you?
Shall we start?
What's going on here?
That's the one from yesterday.
If you come with Flinton, this is the one.
The Russian government and President Erichin seem to have made a big move.
It's not El, it's Erichin.
Let's move on.
What?
There is a rumor that a Chinese woman died in Gawashima.
Yesterday, an accident occurred in China.
The Chinese plane was taken by two Chinese people with weapons and landed at Taipei International Airport, Taiwan.
The culprit was caught and there was no witness.
That was good, wasn't it?
Shall we move on to the last news?
Yes, please.
The last news is...
This is the next news.
This is a scoop.
Oh, it's gotten bigger.
The face is hidden.
It's a round of applause for Mikan Seijin's promotion.
Yesterday, the Mikan Seijin showed off the existence of the Mikan in a big way, and it was officially praised from Ichien-ren.
The reason for this is that all the elementary school students are staring at the orange-faced man in the middle of the school lunch.
It's a very soothing news.
So, today...
How did you like the show today?
It was great!
Did you have any complaints about the show?
It was fun!
Well, let's wrap up here.
Please look forward to the next episode.
See you next time!
Bye-bye!
Yeah!
Igaru weather forecast!
Good luck!
I'm Toro Toro Tororin!
Well then, I'd like to go to the weather forecast again today!
First, from Okinawa!
It's cloudy inside, thump thump!
It's raining.
Let's go to Kyushu.
The effect is that it will be cloudy soon.
It's going to rain from the evening.
Next, we're in Shikoku!
Where are we going?
We're going to Hiroshima!
Where is Hiroshima?
It's sunny and cloudy.
It's Osaka.
It's sunny and cloudy in the sky of Osaka garden.
Let's go step by step.
The sky in Nagoya is getting darker and darker.
And Nagano is
Ah, I got it now.
The weather in Tokyo, where Dogo-kun and Ruga-chan live, is sunny and windy.
The weather in Niigata is cloudy and rainy from noon.
Yeah, I'm going to have a chicken dinner.
I'm going to have a chicken dinner.
Finally, let's go to Hokkaido.
The weather in Sapporo is cloudy and sunny.
Ah, I want to eat Genghis Khan!
That's all for today's video!
Bye bye!
What are you looking at?
Do you know that song?
It's called KODOMO NANDA YO.
It's going to be released in May.
KODOMO NANDA YO.
I'm Haruo Shikata.
Nice to meet you!
Teach me!
You're a great person!
Good morning, everyone.
Did you wake up?
Today, F1 driver Katayama Ukyo will drive us from Brazil.
Have you ever thought about who you want to be in the future?
For example, a singer or a stewardess.
When I was little, I wanted to be a waitress.
I came to France to become a racing driver when I was 22 or 23 years old.
I made a lot of mistakes.
So now you've finally become a famous F1 driver, but the most important thing is...
First of all, to act with courage I want to work with amazing people in the world To think that you will be the best in the world
Don't be afraid.
Failure comes with a price.
Bigger failure than small success.
If you have something you want to do, do it as hard as you can.
Let's jump out into the world.
Jump out!
Mr. Musashi!
Matsuyo!
I'm Matsusho!
It's the third time for Sorakushitora to win!
After a really happy island, Sorakushitora came back to the mountains.
Anastra has been thinking about the new idea that there is no end to human life and that it will continue forever.
On a quiet night when the wind was blowing, a lightning struck in Zoroastra's heart.
Suddenly, he stood up and said, I love you!
At the entrance ceremony, they are showing their butt!
Takamatsu in Kagawa Prefecture, 8-year-old Masako Furuichi, 12-year-old Akiko Uemura from Otaku, Tokyo, and Hiyaki Maruyama from Yokohama Prefecture in Kanagawa Prefecture!
This is Tomato-chan's phone call.
It's cold in the morning, isn't it?
It's hot!
Even though it's April, you're still wearing Kate's underwear!
Then...
Let's get started!
Okay!
The first question is from Yukari Nagashima from Kisarazu, Chiba.
Let's read it!
I'm scared to go to the bathroom at night, but what should I do to have fun?
Yukari-chan!
Yes!
Are you really scared?
Yes.
Did you see something scary?
I remember seeing something like a ghost.
It's scary, isn't it?
I've gotten scared since then!
I know!
I know what's scary!
Hey, Ugo-go and Luga-chan, are you scared to go to the bathroom at night?
I'm scared!
What are you going to do?
I'm scared of cockroaches.
Actually, tomatoes are scary, too.
That's why tomatoes sing songs only when they go to the bathroom.
I always sing, but Yukari-chan, I'll teach you a special one!
Okay.
U-la-la, u-la-la, u-la-ula de kono yo wa watashi no tame ni aru A-oh!
Yukari-chan, say A-oh too!
That's right!
This blue one is the key!
The ghost will run away with this blue one!
Right?
Yukari-chan, do your best!
Yes!
See you!
Bye bye!
Do your best!
I have someone I like, but I'm the only one who likes him.
What can I do to be in a relationship with the person I love?
Tell me, Takae-chan!
Are you such a wonderful person?
In some parts, I say I like you, but...
I say it, but...
I don't think I'm that scabby.
Scabby?
Luga-chan, I'd like to ask Luga-sensei, a professional lover, how about this?
Tell me!
Luga-sensei!
What?
Aishuu?
I want to know how to do it!
Takae-chan!
I'll tell you how to do it!
You can do it, Takai-chan!
Attack!
You can do it!
I like you.
Let's say it together.
Good luck, Sakai-chan!
Bye-bye!
See you tomorrow!
Let's be helpful to others!
Bye bye!
Oh, my God!
I made a mistake.
The first question is from Saki Nobuyama from Nerimac Toyotama.
Good morning, Saki.
Good morning.
I'm going to ask you a difficult question.
Here you go.
What's the question?
I'm going to ask you a difficult question.
If you go to the right, it gets higher, and if you go to the left, it gets lower.
It's hard.
Do you know, Luga-chan?
I don't know.
If you go to the right, it gets higher, and if you go to the left, it gets lower.
Ugo Ugo-kun, do you know?
I don't know.
You don't know?
Saki-chan, do you have a hint?
An answer?
A hint.
The hint is...
Something that makes sound.
What is something that makes sound, Ruga-chan?
Something like a sound museum.
What could it be?
Ruga-chan!
Rappa!
What?
It doesn't seem like it.
Saki-san, please give us the answer.
The answer?
The answer is...
The answer was the piano.
Oh, I see.
That's a great rocket punch.
Yay!
Thank you very much!
Here's the next question.
The next question is from Shiharu Nakanishi of Adachi Prefecture.
Good morning!
The bread is Portuguese.
The skin is Japanese.
What about the dessert?
What does dessert mean?
Say, Luka-chan.
Saladago.
What the heck is that?
Do you know Ugo-go-go?
It's foreign language.
Foreign language?
Maybe you're wrong.
This is a little difficult.
Jiharu, what is the answer?
The answer is food.
Oh, that's so funny!
That's it for today, but let's do our best tomorrow!
Yes!
Lastly, let's do a rocket punch!
Ready, rocket!
Hey, old man!
Go, go, Luger!
We've been connected since last night.
THE END
Speaking of funny jokes, there's this one.
You don't like it at all?
Let's have you laugh today as well!
Naniwa's beauty manzai, Sen'nichi-mae Chinatsu-an's Chiaki!
Let's have you laugh!
Hi, I'm Chiaki!
Which way are you looking at me?
Oh, that's right.
You had a bad dream last night, didn't you?
That's right.
President Elchin proposed to me yesterday.
I love you.
I need you.
I want you.
Don't fool around with Non-tan!
Non-tan?
I put Non-tan in my mouth.
Hey, it's Jin-tan!
I can't do it with you!
Hey, hey, hey!
Good morning, everybody!
Senor, senorita, buongiorno, Mr. Torino Utado Aramu.
Today's guest is the vocalist of ORIGINAL LOVE, TAKAO TAJIMA.
Mwah!
Ima wa hama, ima wa tekkyo ataru zo to
I'm flying through the tunnel without thinking I'm flying through the tunnel without thinking
IZ ALBUM will be released on June 6th!
Moriya
Shia, Haya, Hatake, Nohame, Ato, Eto, Tondeiku
OKAY!
BRAVO!
Mr. Hajima, you were a little too high.
You were able to have a good feeling.
It's good, isn't it?
I can't help but feel the sound.
It's a good feeling.
Tajima-kun, how is it?
Me?
Tajima-kun, how is Tajima-san's song?
He's so cool.
Mr. Tajiwa is the vocalist of the band Original Love.
He used to sing the theme song of the TV show Banana Chips Love.
I'm not Tanaka Seiji.
That's right.
Tony has been paying a lot of attention to it since he was abroad.
It was a cool song today.
Please give it up for them.
Thank you.
Okay, okay.
Well then, please look forward to tomorrow's Ugo Go Uta's album as well.
See you then!
Bye-bye!
Looking for men's treasures.
Lunch break.
There's one left.
A rampage.
Hello, would you like to introduce me to the Ugo Ugo Museum?
What's going on?
Comment ça va?
Comment allez-vous?
Let's go!
The first work is by Hamazaki Daihiko, 8 years old, from Chiba Prefecture.
There is a fox around the fox.
Good!
Let's move on to the next one.
Next, we have 10-year-old Yutaka Yoshida from Kanagawa Prefecture.
Let's go to the next one.
The next artist is 9-year-old Noniko Kusanagi from Tokyo.
The title is called, What are you doing, old man?
Old man!
Oya-jimushi!
What are you doing, Oya-jimushi?
I'm putting on make-up!
You're putting on make-up, huh?
That's pretty gross.
Oya-jimushi is popular!
Shall we move on to the next one?
Next is Shiraimarina-chan, 4 years old, from Kagawa prefecture.
The title is Uga-chan's picture.
Let's go to the next one.
Salmon!
Next is Marina's older sister, Elika Shirai, 6 years old.
The title is Baby's Painting.
It's a baby, isn't it?
It's cute, isn't it?
Shall we go next?
Next is Koutaro Mizukoshi from Chiba Prefecture.
He's 8 years old.
He's cute.
He's a robot.
Today, too,
You enjoyed the morning art, right?
Well then, it's time to go home.
See you later!
Bye bye!
Well, Haruo Chikada seems to be disappointed that he couldn't use the joke he had been thinking about.
I'm Masayoshi, the owner of Uchidebi.
I'm always here for you.
Thank you very much.
My sister was active before you were born.
Do you know that?
I don't know.
Really?
That's sad.
Please do your best.
Somebody!
How was the third day of the live broadcast?
It's a live broadcast only this week, so there are two more days left.
The staff of Go!
Go!
GORUGA are not sleeping well, but please cheer for us tomorrow.
That was 30 minutes in a blink of an eye.
Ryuga-chan, you've seen a place you've never seen before, right?
Where is it?
Let's call them.
There might be people who know them.
Let's go!
Let's go.
Okay, that's all for today.
Who is this?
Ryuga-chan, who is this?
There's a rumor that it's Riga's grandpa.
Is that right?
Yes.
That's good.
It's grandpa, isn't it?
Grandpa, wave your hand.
I'm glad to hear that.
Thank you all for watching.
We'll see you next time.
Bye-bye!
Thank you.