Good morning.
How are you?
Let's start with today's words.
Okay?
Okay.
It's a long one.
It's the same as crying and living.
It's the same as laughing and living.
There's more.
This means that no matter how you feel, you will live the same life, so it is better to live with a smile on your face.
That's right.
Laugh, laugh.
Well, for the time being, let's laugh a lot this year.
Yes!
That's why today, we're having a great time!
We're having a great time!
Yes, well done!
Who are you?
Great People!
Good morning, everyone.
Great People of Chinese Cuisine!
Mr. Shu Tomidoku!
Let's make Chinese food!
Today, let's make shumai together.
The ingredients are ground pork, shrimp,
They put it in a bowl and add salt, pepper, soy sauce and sesame oil.
Add some flavor with the egg.
Mix it well.
Mix it well until it becomes sticky.
The point of this dish is to make a knot and wrap it with the skin.
It takes 18 minutes to cook.
18 minutes to cook.
It's a delicious dish that goes well with spicy soy sauce.
It's called ebi shio.
Today, I'll take you to a very fun dance room.
Make a spell in front of the door.
Do you remember the spell?
Yes, I do.
Say it.
Dance, dance, dance, dance.
That's right.
You're not good at dancing on TV, so sit down.
waiting for me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Everybody!
Mr. Tony!
Come on!
Happy New Year!
Oh, it's good!
Toshimo Torito, dance, dance, dance!
Dance, dance!
Okay.
Do you two remember Tony's dance?
Yes, we do.
Okay.
Let's dance together.
Okay?
Okay.
Come on!
And... Peace!
Fieber.
And... Oh, God!
And then...
OK. One, two, three.
OK.
Happy New Year!
Tony's birthday is January 1st.
It's the 26th of this year.
How old are you?
I'm 26 years old.
I was born on January 1st.
I was born and raised by my parents.
You're not going to talk to me like that.
When is your birthday, Rouga?
It's today, January 5th.
Oh, it's today!
Today is January 5th.
That's right.
It's today, right?
Phoebe!
Phoebe.
You don't understand at all, do you?
Exactly.
Happy birthday.
Come on.
To you.
Happy birthday.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY!
To you… Au revoir!
I've got an idea!
Mikan Seijin has appeared.
Happy New Year!
Ugo Ugo Luga!
This is a great plan!
A great plan!
In 1990, Harapoko, a mysterious man who came to Tokyo, discovered the most delicious tonkatsu and shumita in this town.
Hey, I'm coming.
I'm coming.
Oh, that's right!
I was wrong!
Oh, that's fine!
On the way there, the old man comes to his senses.
Every time I see something delicious, I scream with joy that I'm happy.
Don't say that, you idiot!
It's so good!
Let's eat!
Finally, the time has come to eat Tonkatsu.
What is the taste of Tonkatsu?
And what is the true identity of Daisaku?
Let's find out.
Wow!
It's so good!
Okay.
Bye-bye!
Whoa!
I'm waiting for you!
Apple Jojo!
Let's change the year and say it while we're at it!
I am the master of one country and one city.
Well, I am the lord.
The lord is always at my pace.
Thank you for watching
Thank you.
Morning Literature Red and Black, Episode 2
A few days later, rumors spread that Julian and Mrs. Renard had an affair were spread all over the town.
Eventually, the rumor spread so widely that anyone who lives in the city knows it, so Julian had no choice but to move to a town called Busanseon and enter a new school there.
He fixed it with his power.
He was very good at it.
He was recommended by the Pirar god of the palace.
He was the great king of Paris, King Lamour.
I'm sorry, but I have something to tell you.
I don't have enough money to build a castle.
There is nothing else to talk about.
Can you lend me some of your money?
I got it!
No!
Because I left it in the bank.
You left it in the bank?
It's pretty hard.
I'm fine.
How much will you lend me?
One yen.
What's that?
No way.
Anyway, if you don't give it to me, how are you going to use it?
That's why I entrust it to my mom and ask her to take it to the bank.
Does Ruga buy anything?
Because I can only understand 110 years.
But I can do this.
9, 9, 9, 9, 9, 9, 9, 9, 9, 9, 9, 9.
36, 45, 54, 57, 63, 72, 81.
Everyone, don't say it.
2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven...
That's right.
It's easy, isn't it?
Happy New Year!
Yeah.
One, two, three.
Ooga, ooga, looga.
Happy New Year!
Oh, shit.
Good luck this year, Asao-kun!
you
Finally, please teach me the words of my country for the New Year.
Today's word is 毎度.
Say it.
That's right.
Mild coffee is deep.
We sell mild coffee.
We don't sell mild coffee.
It's delicious because it's coffee.
Then let me drink it this time.
I'm going to cry.
Come to my house and show me around the house.
I'm looking forward to it.
Anyway, MAIDO is a convenient word.
Good morning, good afternoon, good evening, thank you for your help.
How are you doing?
Everyone is included in MAIDO.
It's convenient to say hello to everyone.
Hello.
It's nice to meet you.
It's the beginning of the new year and you're acting well.
Now it's time to go home.
I'm going home.
See you next time.
Bye-bye.
It's the beginning of the new year!
Hey!
We're going to be blown away to Mexico!
Help!
Who are you?
Shokutan Zenkai Bari Bari Pararira Pararira
It's getting colder in the new year.
Do you know what you should do if you can't get out of the bed in the cold morning?
Take a bath in the bed.
What?
Here you go, Ryuga-chan.
I'm going to wake up.
Do you wake up early in the morning?
Yes.
That's a good thing.
That's right.
Let's wake up early and do a lot of fun things.
Today, too, we'll see the fastest Ugo-Ugo-Roo and get off the bus.
Bye-bye!