Good morning.
How are you?
Today is the second day of live broadcasting.
Fugogo and Luga are preparing in another room.
There are a lot of guests.
Now, TV-kun will go to everyone's house.
Let's go!
Let me introduce you to the people in front of the TV.
Are you ready?
One or two?
I don't know if I can do it, but I'll leave it to God and try my best.
It's a perfect word for a live broadcast.
Anyway, I had a great time today.
I was able to do a good job.
Good morning!
When it's over, let's go to the cart!
Oh, okay, that's good.
I saw you yesterday, and you were completely out of breath.
This is a correction.
$16 billion was spent on 1845 yen.
This is actually 1150 billion yen.
Yes, I'll miss this.
Today, I'm going to eat French food.
I'm going to eat French food.
It doesn't matter.
Let's check out the news.
It is said that the railroad that was opened in Vancouver, Canada, six days ago was 16 billion dollars from the United States
Listen to what people are saying.
Let's go!
Who is the winner of the Yudomiya Koukei?
Who is the winner of the Koukei?
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's the first time in a long time.
I've heard it all.
Uenomiya high school in Osaka beat Kigan by 3-0.
The Osaka team is really strong.
They have Hanshin, but the other staff members are also in trouble.
Let's go to the next one.
This one is different.
I'm sorry.
Let's go to the next place.
Yes.
Did you watch the movie?
No.
It was yesterday's video.
In the case of the large-scale fire accident that occurred yesterday, the mayor of Oshima Prefecture did not read the report at all.
Shuro-kun, you're not good at this.
Let's move on.
Okay!
It's a vegetable.
In addition to the fact that Kichigin has entered the market, it is also said that it will be the highest in the market with 109 times and 83 times in the end.
In other words, the value of the yen is probably higher.
It's easier to calculate if it's 1 dollar 100 yen.
Shuri, I think you know the problem at all.
I only know this one.
You know the answer to the question.
Did you understand?
It's no good!
It's interesting!
Let's go back.
See you later!
Bye-bye!
You can do it!
Good morning.
I'm Tororin.
I'm so excited today that I'm going to study abroad.
I'm from Okinawa.
I was born in Japan.
I'm going to study abroad in the afternoon.
Let's go to Kyushu!
Let's go to Fukuoka!
I'm in Shikoku now.
I'm still in Shikoku.
I'll go to Shikoku.
It's sunny here in Nankokuto-san's house!
And Hiroshima is...
I'm sorry I skipped the flight yesterday.
Let's go to Osaka.
The sky is so clear today.
Let's go step by step.
Nagoya is full of sunshine.
It feels like I'm in Okinawa.
It's live!
Live!
It's 2 o'clock in the morning and 2 o'clock in the afternoon.
It's a sunny day in the afternoon.
Come on then!
Bye-bye!
Let's go to Sapporo!
Sapporo will be covered with snow and rain.
It's going to be a hot day.
My friends are coming to the studio today, so I'm very hungry.
That's all for today's video!
How is it?
Hello, I'm Fairchild's Yui.
I've brought you some coffee.
I'm a musician, but I've grown a beard.
Tell us!
Great job!
Good morning.
Itoi Shigesato!
Today, we're going to talk about the topic of the useful titan battle.
To enjoy more titan baseball, first of all,
It's very quiet.
You can hear a variety of sounds.
If you can't hear them,
You lose about 70% of the fun of baseball.
70% is a lie.
You lose a little.
If you try to keep that layer quiet, you'll realize how much more interesting it was.
Please keep that in mind for this year's Kyojin Club.
The next thing is to give a useful applause to the fans.
It may seem like an ordinary game, but it's a good one.
You can't tell if that's a good play or not.
At times like that, you can't help but give them a round of applause.
And the players can play like this.
Then the customer will understand, and it will be even better.
If you play well, we'll give you a round of applause!
This year, Kojima played quietly and with a lot of momentum.
This is his team's...
And by becoming a good titan, you can become a good person.
That was my goal in 1993.
I will do my best to support them.
I will do my best.
Go, Go, Luger!
Oh, no!
He's pushing it for two minutes!
What are you talking about?
How many years have passed since then?
My thoughts are still in the world.
Zoroastra went back to the mountains and went to the most happy island.
Zoroastra is the only one who loves people in front of people.
He is going to teach us how to do it He is going to teach us how to do it He is going to teach us how to do it He is going to teach us how to do it
Let's continue!
Baloo's Magic Trigger!
It's the opening of the baseball penance!
When dynamite is put on the pitcher mount at the baseball field, 5-year-old Kiyota Niseki from Fusa City, Tokyo, and 12-year-old Naomi Mizukami from Karasu City, Saga Prefecture,
Biro Biro Art!
Tomato-chan's phone call.
It was cold yesterday, but it was cold this morning, too.
Did you two catch a cold?
No, we didn't.
That's right.
Please take care of your health.
We've got a lot of letters from friends who are struggling to keep their spirits up.
We'll read them to you.
Let's make it warm!
Today, I'm going to talk to Masaru Watanabe from Shimotsuga, Tochigi Prefecture.
Tomato!
I don't have a postcard, but I'll read it!
I'm a 5-year-old crybaby, and I cry once a day.
How can I cure this crybaby?
Masaru!
Yes?
Can you hear me?
Yes, I can hear you.
Masaru!
Masaru, why are you crying so much?
That's right.
Is that so?
Did you cry when you woke up today?
I didn't cry, but yesterday... Did you cry yesterday?
Yes, I did.
Why?
I had a fight with my sister and she scolded me.
Are you such a crybaby?
Yes.
Do you always cry for little things?
Yes, I cry a lot for little things.
Gogo, what do you think?
Is Gogo such a crybaby?
What?
Does it cry when it moves?
Sometimes it cries.
What about you, Luka?
Oh, really?
I'm scared when my mom gets angry.
And when my sister gets angry.
Yes, tomato tears are the sweat of the heart.
I think it's okay to cry when you want to, but...
But Masaru-kun, if you cry even a little bit, even if you cry when you have to, it won't work.
I can't believe you cried in front of Mr.
Potato.
Do you understand?
Yes, I do.
Masaru-kun, do your best!
Yes!
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Are you going to cry again today?
I'm going to cry.
See you later, Ryo-chan.
You three.
I want to give you strength, but what do you want me to say?
Don't cry.
Don't cry?
Shall we go together?
Ready, set, go!
Yes, I understand.
Are you okay, Masaru?
Yes, I'm okay.
Tomato, you're a great crybaby, aren't you?
Somehow, I feel like I'm friends with Masaru-kun.
What?
Haven't you two forgotten?
I haven't forgotten!
Masaru-kun, you really need to do your best!
Yes, I'll do my best!
Three, two, one, go!
Masaru-kun, bye-bye!
Bye-bye!
Uga Uga and Luka-chan, let's talk about your worries tomorrow as well!
Yes!
Well then, bye-bye!
Bye-bye!
Oh, my goodness.
Today, let's do our best not to lose to everyone in front of the TV!
The first question is from Ryo Iwakiri from Hiratsuka, Kanagawa prefecture.
Good morning, Ryo.
Good morning.
Yes.
Then, please say the question.
Where are the frogs, Mr. Frog?
Wani plus Waniwa.
Niwa.
That's correct.
Peep-a!
What did you say?
Washi!
Washi is correct, right?
I did it!
It's rocket punch!
Ryo-kun!
What's wrong, Ryo-kun?
You know...
The words overlap and form a big circle, right?
A big circle, yes.
So, 2 plus 2 is 4, right?
So, you read it as 4, and it becomes 4.
Thank you!
Here's the second question!
Next is from Senju, Agachiku
It's Nakanishi Chiharu-chan's problem!
Good morning, Chiharu-chan!
Huh?
It seems that there is no improvement, so I will go next.
Is Saki Nobuyama of Nerinax Toyotama here?
What do you think?
I don't think this is going to work.
I'm sorry.
I was going to ask you a question, but that's it for today.
Well, see you tomorrow!
BUDDY!
Koyachibushi!
What are you doing?
It's a firework!
THE END
There are a lot of jokes, but the one that suits the morning is... Well, good night!
It's not funny, but let's make it even more funny.
Let's make it even more funny.
Chiyoko-chan, you're getting up early today.
I can't do this anymore.
I want to go home.
Let's go home.
I'm so tired.
We haven't done anything yet.
30 seconds is enough.
Let's go home.
Don't fool around with Non-tan!
Non-tan?
Non-tan means...
Mom, I'm sorry!
That's Tantan!
They're looking for treasure.
Boris is looking for rats.
They're rampaging.
Hello, can you introduce me to Musée Ngorongoro?
Bonjour, les enfants.
Bonjour, Papa.
Comment ça va?
How are you, Saba?
I'm fine, thank you!
Let's go see Shiro's morning art!
ICHIKAWA City, Shigehara, Kazami-chan, 8 years old.
He's a grumpy boy.
It's a masterpiece that expressed the pain of the heart.
The next one.
Yokohama, Yokohama, Yokohama, Yokohama, Yokohama, Yokohama,
It's time for the next one.
8-year-old Masamichi Kondo from Kitashushu City, Fukuoka Prefecture.
Shuri's son.
He's fat.
The color of his face is also different.
What do you think?
He looks just like me!
Just like Ugo-kun!
As expected.
Shall we move on?
Tomoyo Wada from Saitama Prefecture.
It's a little dangerous, but Shuri looks different.
Shall we move on?
He's Kato from Yokohama City.
Let's move on.
Tenjiko Shinoguchi from Nagano Prefecture.
The Mikan Seijin was amazing today.
It was fun!
That's right.
But it was a refreshing morning.
I'm going home.
Bye-bye!
Well, today's live broadcast seems to have made a lot of mistakes.
Let's go for a drink!
Good morning!
I'm Hano Aki!
I have a very happy announcement for you today!
The ending theme is Ugo Guruga-chan and me, Hanaaki!
How was the live broadcast of Go!
Go!
Luger today?
Well, I think it went well, but did you notice that Gachapin and Mook were there?
Well then, TV-kun will return to the studio tomorrow.
Bye-bye!
I don't know if it went well or not, but how was it?
It was amazing!
It was fun.
I think it was easy for the second day.
One last word, please.
Noruka-soruka.
The meaning is the same as the first word, Uchikabashi.
I'm not sure about the results, but we'll leave it to fate.
Let's do our best tomorrow!
Are you okay?
Let's hurry.
Anyway, see you later.
Bye-bye.
Buta-kun's Yonaoshi Dokkan-tai!
I'm so excited!
Eh?
How many seconds left?
I have to wrap it up?
Eh?
Good bye!
Ah!