This way.
Good morning.
Today's word is, congratulations.
Congratulations.
On New Year's Day, or at a wedding, or at a celebration like that, right?
Yes, yes.
Well then, congratulations.
Oh, I got it!
Congratulations!
Omedetai-hito means a person who is good at everything.
So even if you're called a happy person, you can't be happy.
Got it?
Yes!
Well then, today too, let's have a happy, cheerful, and joyful day!
Happy, joyful, and joyful day!
Yes, well done!
Who are you?
Nekitoros Torotoros Torotoros Torotoros Torotoros Torotoros
Good morning, everyone.
Mr. Shuu Tomijoku!
Let's make Chinese food!
Today, let's make fried eggs and noodles.
The ingredients are eggs, flour...
First, break the egg into a bowl and cut the bottom into small pieces.
Then, season with salt, pepper, soy sauce and sesame oil.
Make sure it's well seasoned.
Mix the eggs well.
Put oil in a frying pan.
Pour the egg into the pot and stir it with a spatula.
The point is not to fry it too much, but to make it look raw.
Don't fry it too much, just make it soft and fluffy.
The soft part is the best part.
If it's too difficult for you, you can ask your mother.
Mikan Seijin has appeared.
Hi.
Good morning.
Good morning, my cute children.
How are you?
Thank you.
Wait a minute!
What?
I made a mistake.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
I said kiki even though it was Karta.
What was I saying?
You forgot, didn't you?
No.
Do you want to try again?
I forgot to say thank you in French.
Ah, it's Merci, isn't it?
Ah, yes, yes.
Say it again.
What was the first thing you said?
Good morning!
Good morning, my cute children!
Merci beaucoup.
By the way...
Happy New Year.
It's better to leave the yearbook at the bank or post office than to leave it to your mother.
We wish all the children prosperity New Year.
Peace, love and happiness.
Thank you very much.
We love Japan.
Thank you.
Happy New Year!
Uga Uga Luga!
Mr. Harako Kozai, a mysterious man who came to Tokyo in 1995.
He was about to eat freshly fried tonkatsu.
Go!
Five minutes after he starts eating, all the bones in the store disappear into his nose.
What is this?
It's a gift from my mother.
The plan was to put oranges instead of money to show how delicious the restaurant's food was.
In other words, instead of Michelin stars.
Don't worry about the tangerines.
Pay for the money.
I can eat more tangerines than money.
What did you say, idiot?
I don't have any money, so I won't take it.
The story continues in the next episode.
Hinshun, Kimete Kimete.
Kessho.
If you were to give up your savings, which would you choose, the bank or your mom?
The bank!
Mom!
Mom?
Mama is a little dangerous.
Shure used to say to Mama,
I gave you all the money, but you took it all.
So you'd better not give it to your mother.
Why?
It seems like my mother used all of them for her clothes.
Let's move on to the next question.
Luka's mom doesn't do such things.
Luka's mom is very kind.
Is that okay?
Oto no Hakubu-san!
Thank you.
.
Morning Literature!
Akadokuro Episode 3 Julian started to live in Paris.
As he had more opportunities to meet rich and wealthy people,
From the time I lived in the countryside, I became a cool man that I could not imagine.
Mathilde, the daughter of Count Lamor, said, I'm beautiful, smart, and elegant, and I won't let you down
Even though she grew up in the countryside, she was very interested in Julian, who was full of confidence, and she gradually started to like him.
And when Mathilde gave birth to his child, he told his father, Rameau, that he would die if he didn't marry him.
It's time for the earthquake joke episode.
Here it is.
The anniversary of the collapse of Russia.
Soviet Union 1st anniversary.
Shibu-kun has collapsed.
Let's do it again.
Decide, decide, Jijin-neta-hen.
After all, the anniversary of the collapse of the Soviet Union is difficult.
Freedom and bread.
Which do you want?
Yes.
Free!
What about you, Ruga?
I see.
It was a clean decision.
What is a free-for-all?
A free-for-all is a paper for drawing.
I see.
Here we go.
Next.
La Questión.
Decide, Decide, Life.
I knew it.
Here we go.
Michael Jackson and a lot of lost people.
Which one is noisy?
Michael Jackson!
Michael Jackson.
How about you, Ugo?
I'm the same as Rika.
Michael Jackson does this, right?
Yes, he does.
It's very similar, right?
My name is Luka.
I live in Pasco and I live in Bagontawan.
That's what I do.
The king of the sea and the king of the night.
Which do you want?
Me!
Go ahead.
You don't know both, do you?
Tohkai Teio is the name of a horse.
It's the name of a horse racing.
The king of the night is the one who makes people go vui vui in the city of night.
He's like our producer.
Jo of the night!
Jo of the night?
Jo of the night might be another producer.
I'm sorry I left you alone.
But you might be good at playing at night.
Playing at night...
Yes.
The queen of the night.
It's very scary.
Excuse me, I dropped some money.
I love you.
Oh, a manzaishi who can't be put in.
The poster is messed up.
Happy New Year!
Thank you.
Boom, boom, boom.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Good luck this year, Masao!
My first dream and my first love.
Question!
My first dream is to see you on the second day of the new year.
My first love is to fall in love for the first time.
Which one makes you happy?
The first one.
Your first dream?
Yes.
What about you, Ugo?
It's a dream.
I see.
It's like you two don't understand at all.
Well, here we go.
I see.
Here we go.
Here's the last question.
La question dernière.
Osechi no datemaki to iitomaki-maki.
It's a song you promised to sing this year as well.
Please sing along.
I see.
So, Shuru will go back to France.
See you!
Ciao!
Bye-bye!
The real Sakamoto-san is here!
We're going to be blown away to Egypt!
The gay pyramid!
We're going to crash!
Who are you?
I'm from Finland!
You're so cute!
One last word that is appropriate for the new year.
Okay?
Okay.
A ship that is about to sail.
Yes, it means to do it to the end.
I'm sure a lot of new things will start this year, but let's do our best until the end.
Yes!
Then, see you again today!
Bye-bye!