Happy New Year!
This way, please.
Okay, thank you.
Today, we'll be using words that are appropriate for the new year.
Okay?
Okay!
One year's salary is in the bank.
This means that the goal of living this way this year is to think about the New Year.
Did you two think about the New Year this year?
I haven't thought about it.
You haven't thought about it at all, have you?
Yes.
All right, then.
Happy New Year!
Who are you?
I'm the father bug.
Congratulations.
Today, let's make potato soup together.
The ingredients are potatoes, seasonal green beans, and ground meat.
It's like this.
It's very easy.
I don't like potatoes.
Boil the potatoes well and crush them.
Put the mashed potatoes aside.
Then, fry the meat in a frying pan.
Then pour in the soup.
If you don't have soup, pour in hot water.
Then add the soup base.
We add all the green beans and potatoes.
We make a thin batter to make the torogi.
That's how it's made.
Thicken with potato starch.
This soup is very warm in this cold weather.
It's delicious.
The sage appears.
Mochi, mochi, mochi, mochi, mochi, mochi, mochi!
Happy New Year!
Thank you!
Here we go!
Ready, go!
Don't get in the way of our date!
What should I do?
Is it too early?
I think I can sing well this year, too.
It's New Year's Eve!
On New Year's Day, we'll have octopus, and we'll spin a ball and play.
On New Year's Day...
Isn't it over?
Really?
The New Year should be over by now.
What day is today?
It's January 4th, right?
January 5th.
One day, Luger will be born!
Happy New Year.
The New Year's Day doesn't seem to come as often as it used to.
One, two, three, go.
Ooga, ooga, ooga, ooga!
Happy New Year!
Yeah, rage on!
Yeah!
OK.
Uga uga ruga.
Happy New Year.
In the winter of 1995, the city of Hanano was at the entrance of Tokyo.
A young man had just arrived at Ueno station.
Oh, here it is!
This is Tokyo, where all kinds of delicious food gather!
Let's eat and eat and eat!
His name is Daisaku Harapeko.
He came to Tokyo to eat delicious food from all over the world.
Other than that, we don't know who he is.
It smells like foreign food!
Oh, this smell!
The Harapiko strategy.
It's a mysterious power that allows him to draw a picture of the past 500 meters away.
Saku Chodai suddenly ran over.
Oh, it's coming this way!
Did Makamon eat it?
There's a shop in a quiet corner.
There was a 25-year-old father on the road.
I'm sorry!
I'm starving!
Who is this man?
The mystery calls the mystery.
Mr.
Potato finally gave me a call.
Then he said he'd cut it off.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Did you get a phone call?
Listen to the story.
This is Luger's house.
Goodbye.
Do you want to listen to my story?
Yes.
Really?
It's a real museum!
Morning Literature Lesson 1 Red and Black
There was a young man named Julian in a town in Switzerland.
He was strongly admired by the great hero Napoleon.
One day, Julian became a family teacher for a child of Renard, who was a butterfly.
He met Mrs. Renard and fell in love with her.
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
You'll fall in love with me.
What?
Mrs. Renard also fell in love with him, and they started to love each other more and more.
Next time, when I call him, I'll tell him that I'm going on a date with him.
I'd like to, but... What's a killer monk?
Something that makes you want to go on a date with me.
What do you think I should do?
Please give me a good answer.
Tell me before you die.
Ugo Ugo God, please.
I won't tell you.
I'm so surprised!
You can write a New Year's card.
A New Year's card?
No.
I already wrote it.
It's a letter.
New Year's letters are almost the same.
Really?
They're the same.
Why are they so similar?
You can't ask me that.
What do you write on New Year's Eve?
That's right.
It's coming this year, isn't it?
Today is January 4th.
January 5th is Ruka's birthday.
I want her to come soon.
Happy birthday to you.
The ambition of a non-selling manzai writer.
The story of the first TV.
Three days later.
Look out!
Whoopi, do you hear?
Hi, Mom.
Ooga ooga looga.
Happy New Year's.
Love and peace.
Oh, yeah
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
It's my birthday this year, Masao!
In fact, Mr.
Potato is called Mr.
Vegetable.
There's a rumor that she went to a hair salon with a beautiful shiitake mushroom.
That's right.
It's called Miss Vegetable.
So you two are lovers?
Did you hate me?
Then you should be with Celery-kun.
Celery-kun?
Celery alone is perfect.
Wait.
I have a question.
Who did you ask about tomatoes?
About the rumors?
Yes.
My friend's tomatoes.
Eh.
Eh?
I asked my friend, Tomato.
Are there two Tomatoes?
There are a lot.
Of course.
Tomato's mom said
Tomatoes.
That's right.
Mom likes tomatoes, too.
Also, tomatoes...
Your country is full of tomatoes.
Hmm.
I learned it from the beginning.
I think I have to be strong this year.
Thank you so much for today.
Yeah.
Please take care of me this year, too.
Then, let's go home together!
Let's go home together!
Bye-bye!
Toshidohajime no Toshidama!
He's been buying a lot of toys until the end of the year!
Sakamoto, the real deal, is getting beaten up by Guryan Guryan!
I'm going to be blown away by the wind!
Who are you?
I am the great Obugyo-sama, Pandani.
The dream you see on August 2nd is called your first dream.
I'll teach you the words of your first dream, okay?
1.
Fuji 2.
Taka 3.
Nasubi
NITAKA 1 FUJI 2 TAKA 3 NASUBI
I don't know.
My first dream... Can I say it?
The first thing that happens to me in my dream is that Mt.
Fuji is the best.
Takaga is number 2, and Nasubi is number 3.
But there's no one who dreams of Nasubi.
What is Nasubi?
There's no one who dreams of the same thing, right?
Yeah.
Well then, I'll see you again next year!
Bye-bye!