Good morning.
Good morning!
It's slanted.
Oh, it's slanted!
It really is!
Good morning.
March is over, isn't it?
I'm looking forward to the live broadcast from April 5th.
It's the perfect time for that.
Are you ready?
Yes!
Hikkomi ga tsukanai.
That's right.
When you get here, you have no choice but to do it.
Ugo and Luga don't like to be thrown out in the middle, do they?
They said they'd do a live broadcast next week, so they won't be able to do it.
Let's do our best.
That's all for today.
Have a good day!
or trouble.
Not too much, sitting back
Hi!
Good morning!
In French, it's called Nouveau in Japanese.
It's not a candy, it's called Nouveau.
In Japanese, it's called Nouvelle.
Nubelberg?
Yes, Nubelberg.
There's Godard and Triforce.
We did it.
Well then, let's go.
Is it okay to decide?
Decide, Decide Special.
Ugo Ugo Lugahen.
Here we go.
Question 1.
Koi de yuuka and Koi de ikoka?
Which word do Kansai people use on a date?
Koide yuka
The second one.
Let's say it's a boat.
It's a boat.
Now, the question is...
Asano Bun-gaku and Nasa no Ken-gaku.
Which do you prefer?
Asano Bun-gaku!
Do you understand?
Yes, I do.
Do you understand the story?
No, I don't.
It's fine if you remember the author and the name of the work.
The questions are... Mikan Seijin and Tanaka Seijin.
Who used to sing Beautiful Sunday?
Tanaka Seijin!
That's right.
Do you know him?
It's not Tanaka Seijin.
That's right.
They don't talk.
Well...
They only say, oh, oh, oh.
That's right.
Here we go.
Question.
Non-tan and Wan-tan.
Which will make you hungry?
Wonton!
Then, Non-tan or Pee-tan?
Which one?
Which do you prefer?
Pintan!
Non-tan or Gyutan?
Gyutan!
I was a little persistent.
I like Masao-kun, the Pufferfish.
The Pufferfish and...
Momohiki's dad.
Which one do you want to be at home with?
Momohiki's dad!
Momohiki's dad.
I can do it!
Go ahead.
It's an imitation, isn't it?
Yes.
How about Michael?
Michael's toys.
He lives here.
It's a small igloo.
What about Momohiki's father?
Is he wearing a momohiki?
What is it?
It's a warm one that my father wears under his pants.
It's a very warm one.
It's a warm one, right?
Do you wear it?
It's open.
It's open?
It's a good family, isn't it?
It's probably a peaceful family, isn't it?
It's a good family.
It's a happy family with a dad with a peach tree.
My dad is also wearing it.
Is he wearing it and purring?
Your mother is wearing it too.
My mother?
She's not wearing it.
Question 6.
You are happy with Tajima Hidetou, right?
Tajima Hidetou or Mito Natto?
Which is more famous in Ibaraki?
Tajima Hidetou!
Don't be shy!
What about school?
What about you, Yuka-chan?
Not Yuka-chan, Ruga!
What about you, Ruga-chan?
What?
Are you famous for that?
You're shy.
Let's go.
Question set.
The one who is great at teaching and the one with a big butt.
Which one do you want to meet?
The person who taught me!
Who has a big butt?
No!
I don't like it.
Question, you eat.
Oshigoto ippai hoi sassa to.
Oshigoto hontou ni ippai erai koccha.
Which one does the Uogoruga staff always go to?
Yes!
The first one.
You have a lot of work to do.
How about you, Hajima-kun?
It's hard, isn't it?
It's hard to prepare for the live broadcast, isn't it?
You two should do your best, okay?
Yes!
Then, Radio Nyaku Question.
Shuru-kun doesn't like it, but the director's time is running out.
And Ito-maki-maki
Which one do you like?
It's been a while.
I'd like to hear it.
Go ahead.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Angelica, you're so beautiful!
Angelica!
Ah, to have lived,
And that's it for this video.
Thanks for watching!
I love you.
I'm going home now.
See you later!
Bye bye!
Let's do it again.
Ready, go!
Kick!
Gompi-tabu-tabu, gompi-tabu-tabu!
Good morning!
How are you?
Good!
We've done a lot of things since we first met, haven't we?
But every single one of them was short-lived, wasn't it?
So, do you remember what you did?
Yes, I do!
What was the first thing you did?
Chiritori!
You remember so well!
Then, how about our unknown name, Twinpix?
I know!
Tsuru!
Ugo-kun!
Tsumiki!
Tsuna!
It's a hornet, isn't it?
A hornet.
All right!
That's enough!
I guess I didn't live long enough to know!
Thank you.
All right.
I see.
Then, do you remember what you did after the game?
Me too!
You guys really remember well.
Yes.
Alright, then let's do an if-and-if attack!
Okay!
First, I'll ask Ugo-go-kun.
If...
If you take a day off, who do you want to play with?
You can think a little.
I'll think a little.
I see.
Okay, I'll ask Ruga too.
You know, Ruga said something about my mom.
I see.
That's a good idea.
Well then, I'll ask Luka-chan too.
If Ugo Ugo-kun had a day off, who would you like to play Ugo Ugo instead?
Ugo Ugo's dad!
Ow!
My thumb!
Maseo!
Do you remember what happened after the attack?
It's coming!
Wait a minute.
What is it?
Did you do it?
I did it!
You're the worst!
The first attack?
That's right!
Let's start with the first attack!
Okay!
What is the best thing about playing Ugo Ogo Luga?
What is the best thing about Ugo-goro?
Don't you get it?
Yeah!
Did you get a lot of toys?
Alright!
See you later!
You know a lot, Oda-san!
Masao!
Do your best, Masao!
Well, well, and the last one is always the dissatisfied pig.
Dissatisfied pig, dissatisfied pig.
Why are we the only ones who have been reborn so many times?
I want a game like this.
My, my collector.
Eh?
What's a live broadcast?
It's about Google Earth.
You guys don't know either, do you?
Yeah.
I forgot to tell you earlier.
Babu!
Ah, that's right!
Director's...
If you make a mistake in the live broadcast,
I can't go.
I made a mistake.
If I make a mistake, I'll just take it.
Well, anyway...
Let's do our best!
Yeah!
Let's keep up the good work!
Alright, I'm going home now!
Okay!
See you!
Bye-bye!
E-bye bye bye bye!
you
Matzo!
Da-da-da, da-da-da, da-da-da, da-da-da!
One last thing.
It's perfect for the live broadcast starting on April 5th.
It's hard.
Yes.
If you do, you'll be saved.
That's right.
When a person is trapped and driven into a desperate situation,
but it also means that you'll be able to come up with good ideas.
Yes!
Before the live broadcast, it's hard for the staff members to feel this way.
That's all for today.
We'll see you again on the live broadcast.
Bye-bye!