me too
Good morning.
It's upside down.
Good morning!
Friday is the day of breakfast.
I'll teach you the words of food, okay?
Okay!
Yaki-mochi wo yaku.
Yaku-pimochi wo yaku.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Here you go.
Please hold it in your hand.
We don't bake rice cakes that are too close or too far away.
To be envious of someone and to be rude to them.
Well then, today, let's have fun!
Let's have fun!
Good job.
Who are you?
You're so cool!
Good morning.
Today, let's make delicious fried rice with everyone.
How to make fried rice First of all,
Egg, white rice, rice, char siu, and sausage.
If you cook the bread well, the smoke will come out.
Then add the oil for the first time.
Add the eggs and fry until they become fluffy.
Next,
Add rice, green onions, and char siu.
It's easier to cook freshly cooked rice.
Fry it until it smells good.
If it's difficult, ask your mother for help.
Today, we're going to make a delicious tea with a strong aroma.
Stir-fry well until the aroma comes out.
It's easy to make, so please try making it.
Mikan Seijin is here.
Thank you.
Friday is the day of breakfast.
You've been waiting for a long time.
Do you remember the spell?
I remember.
Say it.
Talk, talk, talk, talk, line up.
Yes, the TV is going first.
Welcome!
Let's eat!
Itadakimasu!
Today is a very delicious New Year's special.
I wonder what it is.
It's so good!
It looks like umeboshi, but it's umeboshi with umeboshi syrup.
Eat both.
How does it taste, Yuka?
It's good.
Who is Yuka-chan?
Excuse me.
She is a friend of Mr. TV.
Yuka-chan.
How do you feel, Yuka-chan?
It's pretty sour.
I thought it was sweet.
Please eat it with okayu.
Today's dish is Ugo Ugo Lugafu with Nanakusa Kayu.
What year is this?
Saru.
It's the year of the bird.
This year it's the year of the bird, so there's chicken in it, and the two of them are dressed in pio-pio.
Then if it's the year of the monkey, we'll put monkey meat in it.
You can't do that.
You can't eat monkey meat.
Yes, that's right.
Yesterday...
I ate chicken at school on Monday.
It was New Year's Day on Monday.
Did you eat chicken at school?
Yes.
What did you eat, Ruga?
You know, I ate a chicken leg from my school.
Yo!
If you're always in the mood for New Year's, it's going to be tough later on.
Happy New Year!
Thank you very much.
Ugo, Ugo, Luga.
Ugo, Luga, Luga, Happy New Year.
No, Daisaku!
No, Nan-Ki.
We have to save the person in trouble.
She is the female reporter of Nico Nico Times, Sumiko Yamada.
I'm sorry for the interruption.
No, it's okay to thank me.
The reason she came here is to introduce this tonkatsu restaurant to you.
However, it is said that the tonkatsu here has been eaten up by the great work.
Wow!
I'll give him a surprising voice.
You're really great, Fuji-chan!
Wait!
Suzy decided to introduce this tonkatsu restaurant as a restaurant where you can eat a lot of delicious cabbage and rice.
Daisaku is eating a mountain of cabbage and rice one after another.
Otsu is so good!
It's so good!
Suji was so impressed that he invited Suji to go to all the stores in Tokyo.
Kyon's plan to make two friends was to make Tokibo proud that he would keep eating.
The End.
Nanakusagai, was it good?
It was good.
How about greetings?
Do you remember the spell to go back to your room?
Yes, I do.
Say it.
We will go back to the TV.
Peek-a-boo!
Go!
Good morning!
Good morning, Ogurt!
You're going to get a lot of nosebleeds this year, too.
This year's goal is to be in a good tempo.
Did you understand?
I don't understand.
Oto no Hakubu-san!
Morning Literature!
Red and Black!
The Final Episode
Julian, who was arrested, sincerely regretted what he had done so far, and met Mrs. Renard, whose wounds had healed, and felt happy again.
On the day of the trial, Julian was told that it was all your fault.
Julian was told that it was all your fault.
After that, Mathilde held Julian's neck and held a grand funeral, and Lady Renard hugged the children and left this world.
The End.
This year, 1993... What's that?
This year, this year...
This year, 1999...
One, two, three.
It's 1993 this year!
So what?
You don't know?
Of course I do!
That's embarrassing!
I know.
You do?
Now?
This year.
This year?
Like next year?
Last year was 1992.
So, this year is 1993.
Yes.
Okay?
Okay, here's the question.
Yes.
What do you want to do the most this year, 1993?
Hey, Rouga-chan.
I want to keep playing Go!
Go!
Rouga.
Because it's fun.
I see.
The next one is a series of places I've been to.
It's the scariest place I've ever been to.
See?
It's the scariest place you've ever been to.
What kind of place was it?
A haunted house.
A haunted house?
I'm scared.
There is a good place.
Wait for me, Ruga.
The place where my mother got angry.
Manzai Shibuya-bou
I lost all my work.
What should I do?
The end.
One, two, three, go.
Lugo Lugo Hookah.
Happy New Year.
Happy New Year from Great Britain and John Major.
Oka oka loka and a happy new year!
To all the children in the world!
Heal the world.
We'll heal the world together.
Ooga, ooga, looga.
Happy New Year.
Heal the world.
We love all the children.
Of the world.
Ooga, ooga, looga.
Peace.
Goodbye.
Thank you.
Boom, boom, achi gato boom
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Good luck this year, Masao!
Which is your favorite store you've been to so far?
The U-Ga's store.
It's a paper shop.
Where is it?
What about you, Ugo-go-kun?
Well, I want to go to Yurakucho.
A store.
What's a store?
It's next to a toy store.
What kind of store is it?
A restaurant.
Is it good?
Yes.
What did you eat?
Well, I'll teach you.
Ta-da!
What is that?
If you forget, you'll say it's a secret.
I won't tell you, Jean.
Yeah, look at that.
It's a secret again.
It looks like you're angry.
I'm not angry.
Well then, that's all for today.
Yeah, yeah.
Well then, bye bye!
Bye bye!
It's the beginning of the new year!
We're going to the Lingerie Pub!
Who are you?
I'm a student from Kamata!
Lastly, can I teach you another word that comes with the word mochi?
Yes!
It comes with the word shirimochi.
You know this one, right?
You get it, right?
Yes!
Here you go.
If you fly from the stairs, you'll get a shirimochi.
We'll put it on.
We'll put it on the butt.
You two slide on the snow and don't put it on the butt.
See you next time!
Bye-bye!
See you next week!