He's watching a behind-the-scenes show at 7.30 in the morning!
Sakamoto, who hasn't played in a while, is getting beaten up by Maki-moku-moku!
Finally, the long-awaited show begins!
Udo and Toruga are waiting in another room.
Today, TV-kun will go to your house.
Let's go!
It's a word for everyone in front of the TV.
Even though he doesn't know much about it, if he starts talking to the police, he will fail a lot.
We'll do our best not to say OK on the live broadcast.
With that said, OKIRAKU GOKURAKU OKIRAKU GOKURAKU Yes, we did it.
Good morning!
Today is April 5th, Monday.
It's 7.31.33.
Everyone in front of the TV is at the same time, so this is a live broadcast.
I'm excited.
So, what are we going to do today?
7th round news.
News!
It's news.
I'm the caster, and I'll explain to Kuogoi-kun and Luga-chan.
Well, I don't know what it's going to be, but please explain.
Yes!
Before the news gets out,
The studio is also excited.
Before we move on to the news, let's have Shuru say a few words of apology.
Excusez moi.
That's right.
If you make a mistake, you have to say, excusez moi.
If you do that, you'll get hit, so be careful.
Alright, let's get started.
The price formation.
It started in Vancouver, Canada on the 4th day of the Japanese time.
At the beginning of the day, President Clinton of the United States and President Ericsson of Russia
The total cost is 1.6 billion dollars.
It's shown in the plan.
Today, on the 2nd, the issue of financial security has been discussed and the declaration of co-operation has been announced.
It's hard.
Did you understand the story?
I don't understand.
I don't understand what Silk is reading.
By the way, do you know Kurinton?
Yes, I do!
We've seen Kurikinton and many others before.
Clinton is the president of the United States.
Clinton will give $1 billion to the Russian agent.
That's about 2,840 billion yen.
5th place.
What would you like to buy?
Let's move on to the next one.
De La Formation 2.
The semi-finalist wins.
The SEVA Low League Tournament is...
It's the 4th day.
I'm so excited.
The 4th day.
The winner's and the loser's rounds will be held.
The Parig Tournament will be held in Nippon Ham.
HANSHIN won 3-0 against KUKANPU in the middle of the race.
He won 20 million yen.
As expected.
As expected, Osaka people are strong when it comes to money.
But Kiryu-kun is a yakuza fan.
Please do your best.
Let's move on to the next one.
Let's see the weather information.
Here it is.
It's a Chinese woman.
It's a Japanese-style incident.
Oh, is it only 1 minute and 30 seconds left?
It's been a while since I've been here.
It's in the east of Oki in Togoshima prefecture.
On Tuesday night, Hokkaido's TAKEMASU FOOTBALL GAME will be played by 145 people from China.
I can't read any of them.
What should we do?
In other words, the Chinese have joined Japan.
It's Mikko.
He's making a lot of mistakes.
At times like this, you can say, excuse me.
In other words, it's a secret country.
Have you ever heard of a foreign country?
Well, I don't think so.
Well then, let's go home, Shulgu.
Yes!
We're going to the supermarket today, but we're going to do it tomorrow.
We're going home now.
Bye-bye!
Ugo-go weather forecast.
Good morning, I'm Tororin.
Let's take a look at the weather all over the country.
First, let's take a look at Okinawa.
Naga seems to have a bad eye from time to time.
Now, I will land in Kyushu.
Yes.
What about Kyushu?
Fukuoka is sunny and sunny.
It's cloudy in the morning.
Let's go to Shikoku this time.
Nangokuto is sunny and cloudy.
Ta-da!
Finally, we're in Osaka!
The southern sky is sometimes cloudy, and in the morning, it's a bit cloudy.
Ta-da-da-da!
Next is Nagoya.
Nagoya is sunny and cloudy.
Let's go to Tokyo.
It's cloudy in Tokyo.
Let's keep going.
We're going up to Niigata.
Niigata is a place where it rains or snows when it's cloudy.
It's already spring, and it's snowing.
And Sendai is sometimes cloudy.
Let's keep drinking.
Let's go to Hokkaido and Sapporo.
Sometimes it's cold, and sometimes it's snowing.
It's cold all over the country.
That's all for Tororin's Ugo Ugo Tenkyouhou!
What did you do today?
I did math and math.
How was it?
Oh, good morning.
My name is Hayashi.
Hello.
Today is April 1st, Tsurumaru's birthday.
Tomorrow is April 3rd.
Good morning.
My name is Harumi Hosono.
I'll talk about music today.
What do you think this is?
This is a baritone trio.
However, I can hear this in the music.
The locals don't make this as a musical instrument.
If you make a sound, it becomes a musical instrument.
Each of these sounds are just bamboo sounds, but the pitch changes a little.
When the sound is higher than one,
I was able to make my own music.
When I was a kid, I used to play with a can.
I used to hit the cardboard and play instead of the drum set.
So you don't need a high-end synthesizer to make music.
When I get home, I hit the can.
I do that many times.
I only listen to insects, but I listen to music.
Music is a familiar thing to me.
I'll remember that.
O-Yajibushi!
No, no, no, no!
As I thought, you have a good name!
He went to the mountains.
He spent 10 years thinking about his life.
After a while, two people gathered in the city and crossed the mountain.
All the gods were dead.
Now we can only live with the power of humans.
After taking the teaching, he returned to the mountain again.
Haru no Ohanami!
If you put a cherry tree in the back of a flower, you'll be like Fujii Daisuke from Sapporo, and Aokiya-sensei from Setagaya, Tokyo.
It's time for Tomato's phone call.
Good morning!
This week, you can't just cry like that!
Ugo Ugo-kun and Ryuga-chan, think hard and let's do our best to find the right answer together!
Let's go!
Let's make a tomato phone call!
Pop, pop, pop, pop!
Congratulations!
Today's consultation is from Nozomi Suzuki of Hamamatsu City, Shizuoka Prefecture, who is 9 years old.
First, Tomato will read a postcard.
My brother is kind, but he doesn't call my name when he calls me.
He calls me monkey, or husband, or Taro.
She wants you to call her properly, so she wants you to tell her what to do.
Nozomi-kun, are you there?
Yes, I am.
Nozomi-kun!
How are you?
Good morning!
Nozomi-kun, are you really born like that?
I'm in trouble.
Is that so?
Yes.
How old are you?
I'm in my second year of college.
Yes.
Is that so?
What do you think, Ugo Ugo-kun?
About being called like that.
That's tough!
What about you, Ryuga?
No!
Yes.
Tomatoes used to be called the power of demijohn when they were very big.
But, Nozomi-kun,
Nozomi-kun!
You know, when people call you a monkey, you say, like, I'm so happy, thank you!
You know, if you keep doing it, you might not be able to say it because it's boring.
I like the way you talk, so I have to stop for a while.
Nozomi, what do you think?
But I like it a lot.
Is that so?
Nozomi-kun, are you playing with the monkeys?
When I was in first grade,
My brother put a ball on the shelf and brought a towel and threw it around.
Yeah!
Well then, Ugo-go and Ryuga-chan, let's do our best tomorrow as well and get through the trouble!
Yes!
Well then, bye-bye!
Bye-bye!
Thank you.
What was that?
You're not going out?
Haha, I'm not going out until tomorrow.
Then, since Ishizawa is doing a live broadcast today, Uogoruga will answer the riddles that everyone in front of the TV has come up with.
Is that okay?
Hi, that's right, that's right, that's right.
Let's start with the first question.
It's a question from Ishii Yasutomo from Matsudo, Chiba.
In Ichi-kun's letter, it says, please call me Tomo-kun.
Tomo-kun!
Can you hear me?
Yes.
Tomo-kun, is that okay?
Then, Tomo-kun, please answer the question.
Yes.
What's a miracle when you play pro-wrestling?
Huh?
When you play pro-wrestling?
A strong tree?
It's a tree, right?
Yes.
Okay, then... Mr. Nuga, do you know what it is?
Is it difficult?
It's difficult.
I don't know.
I don't have time.
I'll be there in 10 seconds.
I don't have time, but what should I do?
Before I say the hint, what's the answer?
Shall I say the answer?
Inoki.
Inoki?
This is so cute!
This is amazing!
It's like a rocket punch!
Thank you, Tomoku.
Okay, let's move on to the next person.
This person is from Minami-ku, Fukuoka.
It's Hayashida Mami-chan's question.
Mami-chan!
Can you hear me?
Good morning!
Please tell us the question.
Okay, I'll do the quiz.
Sokupan and Gansupan were walking
From the back, if you call it Ooi, which do you prefer, Sokupan or Francepan?
French bread!
French bread?
Why?
Grandpa!
What?
What's wrong?
I'll turn around.
It's my first time.
There's no more time.
What's your answer, Mami-chan?
The answer is bread.
Because bread has ears.
This is amazing!
Robot-kun?
Yes?
This is super difficult!
Super difficult?
Well, since we don't have much time, let's do our best tomorrow!
That's all for today!
Bye-bye!
I can't do it.
Ah!
It's spring now.
When spring comes, I play Hakodate with my guitar Why?
Because I play Hakodate with my guitar This is a big hit
Let's take a short break.
This is Okutani from Naniwa's Nishinbanzaiji.
Hello, I'm Jackie.
It's your first time on the stage, but your title is too big.
Don't mess with me!
What?
What are you talking about?
It's you!
Look at that!
Good morning, everybody!
Good morning, kids!
Today we're doing a live broadcast.
For the first week of the show, Tony will introduce some great sounds.
UOGO Song Album Today's guest is my best friend, Yoko.
The song I'm going to sing today is Chichi Kaka.
This is... Chichi Kakashi!
Chichi-ka-ka, chichi-ka-ka, chi-ka-chi-ka-chi The twins, Chichi and Kaka At first
My little girl, come on
What?
Thank you, thank you, Yoko-chan.
Okay, please give a round of applause.
How was it, Yoko?
I'm a big fan of this show, so I had a lot of fun today.
By the way, Yoko-chan, can I ask you a favor?
Yes.
Please give me your autograph.
Oh, I got it.
It's perfect!
Let's try Tony's Go!
Rush!
Now, Luka-chan, Ugo-kun, let's try Ah!
No Okusama!
Let's do it together, Yoko-chan.
I'm sleepy.
And the last one is a big laugh.
Okay!
Thank you, Yoko-chan!
So, please look forward to tomorrow's Ugo Ugo song album!
Now then, see you tomorrow.
Bye-bye.
Men's Search for Treasures
Now, let's find the treasure.
Dig, dig, and dig.
The aquarium.
Alex.
Hello, can you introduce me to the Gorugoro Museum?
Good morning again.
Good morning!
You must be tired.
Let's take a deep breath.
Tony's voice doesn't change much, does it?
The content was a bit too much, so let's call it a day.
Churyu-kun's morning art.
First of all, the first work, please.
This is a work by Shigemitsu Ogiso of Tachikawa City, Tokyo.
What do you think?
It's amazing, isn't it?
This is truly the red of Matisse.
That's right.
Wonderful.
Next work, please.
Sapporo City's...
Hirama Taku-kun.
He looks angry.
It's not good.
Isn't this a work that can be considered to be a high-level impressionist work?
Yes!
Then, shall we move on to the next one?
Here you go.
Yuki Takahashi of Sendai City, 9 years old.
She's wonderful.
This looks like Giacometti.
Let's go right away.
What is this?
It's stuck.
Let's go next.
Otaku's biggest friend, Haseko.
Roboto-kun.
Not-kun's Rocket Punch.
As expected of him.
Children are all artists See you tomorrow!
Bye bye!
you
Yaaay!
It seems that you have to fail to do a live broadcast to have fun.
Good morning!
I'm P.R.
Taki from the Electric Group!
Big brother!
KABUTOMUSHI!
So everyone, how was the live broadcast of Uogoruga?
Was it interesting?
Hayashi Apei-san and Boncho Samu-san, please support us.
We have a great guest tomorrow as well.
TV-kun is going back to the studio now.
It was only 30 minutes, but how was it?
It was fun!
Was it fun?
Yes!
Lastly, I'll teach you one more word, okay?
Tomorrow will be a windy day!
Tomorrow!
That's right.
Tomorrow is tomorrow, so it's better not to be nervous.
It was a live broadcast that you don't know what will happen.
Let's do our best tomorrow.
Are you okay?
I'm okay!
Let's hurry up!
Okay!
Then, let's take off again today!
Bye-bye!
Now, it's the first day of the year.