Mikan Seijin Hour!
Ha ha ha!
Aniki!
On Saging Hour!
Bye.
The one who lives to love
Mikan Seijin Hour!
What?
A person who is kind to everyone, who lives to love
Mikan Seijin Hour!
... ... ... ... ...
Thank you for watching
Ita Seijin Hour!
Everyone is kind, everyone lives to love
Mikan Seijin Hour!
Oh yeah!
Titan Saging Hour!
Father!
The one who lives to love
Mikan Seijin Hour!
I'll get!
What's up?
Mikan Seijin Hour!
Thank you for watching!
Waaah!
.
The one who lives gently in love
Mikan Seijin Hour!
Aniki!
No!
Ikan Seijin Hour!
The one who lives to love with kindness
Saging Hour!
The one who lives gently in love
Dancaging Hour!
The one who lives to love with kindness
Bye.
Saging Hour!
The one who lives to love with kindness
Raya!
What's up, Luka?
Can you apply some oil on me?
Oya-jibushi!
Go for it, Yuga!
It's the first time I've ridden an ambulance, and it's fast!
Mikan Seijin Owo!
Titan Saging Hour!
Mikan Seijin Hour!
Gun Saging Hour!
Seijing Hour!
Saging Hour!
Mikan Seijin Hour!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Dancaging Hour!
It's time for Seijin Hour!
Mikan Seijin Hour!
Mitan Seijin Hour!
On Saging Hour!
Titan Saging Hour!