Welcome!
With gentle words, I brush my eyelashes
Even though I'm a man, I'm cold inside
¶¶
Konnichiwa!
This is a live broadcast!
You can do it if you try it twice a day, right?
Yes!
Did you have a good day?
I did!
Did you pee?
Okay, that's enough.
It's time for the evening words.
MUSEUM ON AIR!
A museum is an art museum.
On air means broadcasting.
Right now, Ugo Goruga's studio is connected to the Futabashi-Kuritsubijutsukan in Tokyo.
Oh, yeah!
At this art gallery, the Media Epoch exhibition is being held.
You two can draw in this studio today.
It was interesting yesterday.
Everyone in front of the TV can participate.
We'll show you what kind of system it is.
First of all, if everyone in front of the TV went to the Utabashi-Kuritsubijutsukan, they would use a computer at the venue to draw, and that would be the museum's...
It will be an exhibition.
People who saw it yesterday will know, right?
I'm happy to see my painting in the museum.
I want to experience it.
Next, children who can't go to the museum can participate in PAX.
Please ask your parents for help.
When you send the fax, it will be delivered to the museum.
I wrote a lot of them.
The ones I wrote at the art museum, the ones I sent to the art museum by fax,
It will be shown live in the studio of Ugo Goruga.
And everyone can watch it on TV at home.
It's new.
Drawing with a computer is very interesting, isn't it?
It moves, doesn't it?
Yes.
You learned it right away, didn't you?
For those who want to go to the museum, I'll explain the location.
Here's the map.
It's located in Itabashi-ku, Tokyo.
Please get off at Takashimadaira Station on the Toei-Mita Line.
Nishiguchi's Takashimadaira library has been fined.
I'm sorry I told you something a little confusing on TV yesterday.
This method is convenient.
There is also a Soge bus from Narimatsu Station on the Tobu Tojo Line.
The art museum is open from 9 am to 4.30 pm.
Please take a good look at the map.
Okay.
You might want to send it by fax, right?
Yes.
I'll show you the number.
Here's the number.
0353835555.
Don't mess up your phone number.
It's not a phone call, so we can't talk to you.
Okay.
Draw your favorite picture and send it to me.
I'm under 12 years old.
Okay.
Today, TV-kun is going to the Itabashi Art Museum.
See you there!
I'm flying.
This is quite eye-catching.
This is the Itabashi-Kuritsu Art Museum.
I wonder if there are many people who watched yesterday's broadcast.
Hello.
I'm walking.
It would be nice if there were a lot of them.
There's a little one, too.
Hello, I'm Terebi-kun.
Hello!
In the studio, we will be drawing again today.
The teacher is Shuru-kun.
By the way, everyone at the venue, please say it with us, okay?
Okiraku!
Gokuraku!
Hello, can you introduce me to the museum?
How are you?
I'm fine!
Next up is a live broadcast in the evening.
What do you do in the evening?
I'll draw a picture.
Okay, let's start with the wall painting.
This singer has gone to bed.
It's already the second day.
You can go to the stage now.
Let's get back to it.
Today, we're going to show them our faces.
It's your own face.
Your own face?
Your own face.
Please draw your own face.
I'm drawing it already, right?
Sure, draw it.
Let's do it quickly.
This is Gogo-kun, right?
Yes.
Ryuga-chan.
Oh, Ryuga-chan has also started.
Your face is a little too thin, isn't it?
Oh, that's right!
But it's okay because it's your ideal type.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
Please draw more and more.
While Uogoto Ruiwa is writing in the studio, Itabashi Kuritsu Museum.
There are children in the Itabashi art museum as well.
Tomoto-chan from the Itabashi art museum!
Hi, Shurikuu!
Bonjour!
How are you?
I'm fine!
It's a tomato!
Ah, it's a tomato!
It's a small tomato today, isn't it?
That's right!
It's a small tomato today!
As usual, the eyes are sparkling and cute, right?
It's cute!
Right now, in this venue, four boys and four girls are drawing.
There are a lot of friends outside the venue.
And so, Pax is also getting bigger and bigger!
Ah, he's getting bigger.
Yes!
What do you think of the kids at the venue?
Oh, then let's see the 8th one, the boys.
The 8th one is a boy?
Yes!
Ah, what is this picture?
A caterpillar.
A caterpillar?
A caterpillar!
What's your name?
Oh, the other one is... Mario-mushi.
What's my name?
Are you Mario-mushi?
Nice!
Kawaii Daishi-kun!
Daishi-kun?
Hello, Daishi-kun.
Hello.
What are you drawing?
Mario?
Show me.
Ah, I see.
Mario, right?
What about the other one?
The old man?
Is there something about this?
What kind of caterpillar?
A normal caterpillar.
A normal caterpillar?
Yes.
Then, draw more and more caterpillars.
Are you ready?
Yes.
I think I'll put in another one.
It's a girl on the third floor.
Well, this picture is...
What is this?
It's a cat.
Oh, it's a cat.
Shure-kun, can you see it?
I can see it.
It's cute.
What's its name?
What's your name?
I'm Chiharu Furusawa.
Chiharu-chan.
How old are you?
I'm 12 years old.
12 years old?
You're good.
Now, the children are drawing as well.
Now, Tomoto-chan.
Yes?
Please show the children on the stage.
Yes.
Can you write your own name?
Yes!
Everyone, please write your own name!
It's a self-portrait.
It's a self-portrait!
You draw a self-portrait, and under it you write your name.
Okay.
Yes!
Please draw a self-portrait and write your name on it!
Tomoto-chan?
Yes!
What about the fax that's coming to the Itabashi Art Museum?
The fax?
There's a lot of them.
I'll show you a little bit.
The one that's flowing over there?
Yes.
How about the one at the venue?
Oh, the one that's playing?
The one I saw yesterday.
It's playing right now.
Can you see it?
Oh, they're coming.
It feels like they've been coming since before the broadcast started.
Really?
Yes.
I have a friend.
There's a tomato!
It seems like yesterday's wish has come true.
That's right!
There are a lot of tomatoes today!
There's a robot, too.
Send it to everyone.
Yes, please send it to everyone.
Well then, Takato-chan.
Yes!
I want to see the Ugo-Odoruga picture first, is that okay?
Okay, then let's see the Ugo-Odoruga picture.
What's this?
Ugo Ugo-kun?
It's my face.
Uwago-kun, do you think your face is similar?
I think so!
You think so?
He doesn't have a nose.
Why are you drawing it?
How about you, Luka?
You look like him.
My eyes and mouth are connected!
Ugo-kun, let's try it again.
Ugo-kun, there's a problem.
My eyes and mouth are connected!
Everyone is drawing.
Let's go to the commercial.
Let's go!
It's about time for the kids to come down.
This is a cute house!
Hello!
Can you hear me?
Hello.
What's your name?
I'm Eiko Kumisaka.
Oh, she has a pretty good taste in her eyes.
MisaSaka-chan?
Eiko-chan?
Shall we look at the picture?
Yes.
Tenko-chan's name is in the alphabet, right?
It's similar!
Viva!
It's similar.
Look at her face.
Then, Shuri-kun, one more person.
The second one is a picture of a boy.
Ah!
You did a great job!
Yuta Nakao!
Yuta-kun!
Look at Yuta-kun's face!
Yuta, do you think you look like him?
Shigeta-kun, what do you think?
Do you think you look like him?
I don't think I look like him.
I don't think you look like him.
Which one is more manly?
Where did Mita come from?
We're in Tokyo.
So, did you watch yesterday's show?
Yeah.
Oh, you came to see the show.
Are you okay?
Yuta-kun, you're in a daze.
Yuta-kun, you were really energetic until just now.
Really?
Maybe you're shocked by your own rotation.
Is that so?
It's okay.
Then how about number 6?
Number 6!
Number 6 is pretty good, isn't he?
Yeah, he's pretty good!
May I ask your name?
What's your name?
What do you think, Yuuki-kun?
It's similar.
Yuuki-kun is similar.
What do you think?
Do you think you look like him?
I don't think so.
I don't think you look like him.
Really?
I think you look like him a lot.
Do you think you look cooler than him?
Really?
Then try drawing a cool picture of yourself.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes.
Then let's go with number 8.
Daishi-kun is really good!
Daishi-kun is really similar!
Daishi-kun?
This is Daishi-kun's face.
What do you think?
Daishi-kun!
Yes!
Daichi-kun, you look like him.
You look like him!
Maybe it would be better if you had a little more bulge.
If you do that, you might get it.
You're good.
It's like a dynamite.
Is it like a dynamite?
Yes.
How about number 7?
Number 7?
Noriko-chan.
Hello.
Did you hear Silk's voice?
Hello, Noriko-chan.
Noriko-chan, how is it?
Did you write it?
Oya?
That's right.
Mariko-chan, is this similar?
What do you think?
It's not very similar.
It's not similar?
Dorito-chan, we don't have much time.
We still have time.
You can keep writing.
Please keep writing.
Let's go with number 3.
Number 3!
This is Chiharu Chiharu.
She's cute.
It looks like him!
Chiharu-chan, have you been practicing this?
No, I haven't been practicing.
You haven't?
Yes.
You're really good.
What do you want to be in the future?
I haven't thought about it yet.
You haven't thought about it?
That's good.
You've been told off.
The first one is good.
I like it.
Ahaha, I love tomatoes!
That's nice.
It's Yuko-chan, isn't it?
Yuko-chan?
Yuko-chan, you're good.
You're good at being bad.
But being bad is good.
You have a good taste.
Let's look at your face.
Do you think you look like him?
I don't think it's similar.
Oh, but it has a taste.
It has a taste, doesn't it?
That's right.
It's better to add color.
Then continue to draw.
Please.
Then, number 4.
Number 4's friend.
Yes.
Ah, it's done.
It's done.
Oh, yeah!
Harashima Yashitaka.
Yashitaka-kun?
Yashitaka-kun is pretty cool.
He's popular.
He's cool.
Nice.
Yashitaka-kun, you're popular, aren't you?
I'm a fan of Tomotomo's Yashitaka-kun.
Did you really become a fan of Otomo-chan?
Yes!
Then, let's go back to the studio.
Uomo-kun, show me!
What is this?
It's so funny!
What do you think of your face?
It doesn't look like me!
How about you, Ryuga?
What do you think of yourself?
Are you sleepy?
Should I shave your cheek more?
But it's similar, isn't it?
It's cute.
Isn't that a smart touch?
Tomato-chan, it seems that everyone has drawn a picture, so please record this picture and ask everyone to draw a picture of you.
Everyone, please draw it cutely!
Try drawing Tomo-chan's face.
Make it beautiful!
Uo and Uga, please draw Tomo-chan's face.
Hurry up and draw it!
I don't think I can draw it.
No, no!
Why not?
You don't think you can draw it?
How do you draw it?
Don't you want to draw Tei-chan?
Please draw with your true feelings, Ugo-kun!
I'm going to draw her.
Well then, Shurikkun.
Yes?
Well then, let's do a fax.
There's a lot of people here, so I'd like to introduce you to some of them.
Is that okay?
Yes, please.
So, are you showing us the whole thing?
Well then, here comes the tomato movie!
Sato Kazuki-chan, 5 years old!
And Kazuki-chan is 5 years old.
Isn't she cute?
She's cute, isn't she?
Then, let's see the picture of the pig.
筋肉豚くん、くまんより上手!
Underneath that, there's a thing called a shurikoyajimushi.
I'm scared!
Also, if you turn right, you can see Tomato-chan.
Do you want to see more of Shu-kun?
There's also a TV.
Yes, it looks like this.
Yes.
How is it moving?
Is it moving?
Yes.
Show us, Goma.
I can only see the skin.
Please show us.
Good.
Ego-kun, write something.
With all your heart.
With all my heart.
That's right.
Ruka-chan, do you want to do it?
Luka-chan is also done.
It looks like everyone is drawing, so let's go to the commercial.
See you in the next video!
It looks like it's almost done.
This is it, right?
Ryuga-chan, you're drawing seriously.
Can you see Ryuga-chan's face?
You look serious.
It's been a while since I've seen you like that.
You always joke around, but you look serious today.
How about you, Uo?
I lost my love for you.
Why?
Huh?
I thought you were weird.
Why?
You couldn't express your love for me?
Yeah.
How about you, Ryuga-chan?
What is this?
Are you showing off?
Tears?
Yes, tears.
There are a lot of tears.
Now, Tobado-chan.
How do you like the venue?
It's getting better and better, and it's fun!
First of all, Chiharu-chan, the third girl, has become like this!
Shiobu-chan?
Yes?
You're good.
It's cute!
It's cute, isn't it?
It's not a crying tomato, is it?
Are you not crying?
You're not crying, are you?
Yes.
It's a strong tomato!
It looks like everyone else is still drawing.
Yes!
How about Fax?
Ah, Robot-kun.
If you go to the right, you can see the TV from Chinami-chan in Gifu prefecture.
It's cute, isn't it?
On the right side, there is also an angry tomato.
And then... Wow, this is good.
Is it?
Shurikun Nagai.
And then?
Shikato Shurikun, do you know him?
Shikato...
It looks like Han-chan.
There's a long Shuru.
It's a Shuru.
Hasuyama Satoshi-kun.
On the right, there's a picture of Go Go Go.
Ayano-chan is 4 years old!
Ugogo-kun?
Give it to me!
Ugogo-kun sent me a picture of you.
What do you think?
Is it good?
Really?
Do you think it's similar?
Are you happy?
What should I do?
Then it seems that number 5 has played it.
The 5th one is written as Hidaki!
I want to see it.
It's Shizuki!
That's cute.
It's done!
It's Shizuki, but it's Shizuki.
Shizuki?
It's done.
Let's go with the first one.
The first one is cute too!
Please show us!
The color is nice.
How is it?
She didn't use red.
But it's a nice color, isn't it?
Yuko-chan, you're good at this.
Yuko-chan, do you like tomatoes?
Let's go to number 8.
Number 8's friend.
Number 1 is drawing his own ship.
Very nice.
Daishi-kun.
Number 8's Daishi-kun.
What kind of image is that?
What do you mean?
Say the truth!
Daishi-kun is pretty good.
Daishi-kun?
I can't say the truth.
Daishi-kun, can you hear me?
Yeah, I can hear you.
Daishi-kun, you have a pretty good attitude.
You're going to be a big star in the future.
You're going to be a big hit in the future.
You're doing your best, aren't you?
Yes.
You're chewing gum, aren't you?
That's good.
That's a good attitude.
How is it?
How about number 6?
Number 6 looks like a friend.
Yuuki-kun!
Yuuki-kun, show me your tomato!
Show me your tomato?
But I like Yuki-kun a lot.
Yuki-kun's art.
Yuki-kun probably really likes Tomato.
Tokada-chan, I'd like to say goodbye to everyone at the venue.
I understand!
Everyone, thank you so much!
Thank you!
We're going back to the studio.
Thank you, Toba!
This is a picture of the studio.
There is a heart on it.
How about Ruka-chan?
Ruka-chan?
What?
She's crying.
As expected of the bold Ruka-chan.
Let's go back, Shuru.
Let's do it again tomorrow.
I'm going to go home now!
Bye-bye!
How was the live broadcast of the museum on air?
Children will quickly remember the drawing of the computer.
Itabashi Kuritsubijutsukan will be broadcast at 4 pm.
How was the museum on-air?
Children will quickly learn how to draw on a computer.
Itabashi-Kuritsubijutsukan is open until 4.30 pm.
Today is the end, so please expect it tomorrow.
It's okay to participate in FACTS.
I'll give you the number.
Yes, 0353835555, 53835555.
Got it?
Well then, TV-kun will go back to the studio.
Today, the two of them looked at the audience closely.
Everyone at the venue was very good.
Thank you very much.
I want you to gather a lot of people who want to draw on the computer.
Luka-chan, it's fun, isn't it?
Let's practice a little more.
Please do your best.
Tomorrow, too, the Newsy Amoyama live broadcast.
Please join us at Itagashi Kuritsubizu-kan!
That's right, there's an announcement, right?
Yes!
Please watch the live broadcast tomorrow!
See you!
Bye-bye!
Let's go!