Natsu no asa, mezamesha, oh!
Mada aru koneko-chan, bravo!
Furi-chin, nama-dashi, nama-nama, hajimari
It's been a while since the last live broadcast.
Let's do our best.
From today to Friday.
Last time, TV-kun went to the house of the people in front of the TV.
Hello, I'm here to talk to you.
I'm going to hell.
I don't know what's waiting for me to do.
This is what it's like when I'm live.
Please support me.
Are you ready?
Okiraku goku raku!
Well done!
Thank you very much.
The radio is amazing.
Can you hear the sun?
Yes!
The sun is shining.
How many days have you been here?
This is Shun-kun's Off-Lance course.
In the Off-Lance course, you can learn about the news.
Let's go!
Let's go right away!
Result Formation 1
Today's En Daka.
Shut up!
Sorry, that was a farce.
I'll take it off from the beginning.
I see.
Finally!
I'm sorry.
Finally, En has entered the 1 dollar 100 yen range.
He has recorded the highest price since the war.
How much is a wrestler's nose?
I don't know at all.
How much is a day's allowance?
So, this is...
You're not giving it to me?
How much is it?
300 yen!
300 yen?
I'll buy the steering wheel.
That's good.
Today's Hoseokawa
It's not Kumin.
It's Prime Minister Hosokawa.
Do you know the new Prime Minister?
No, we don't.
Do you know Ugo?
Well, a week after the new cabinet was adopted, Prime Minister Kasogawa went to a human dock at a hospital in Tokyo yesterday.
I took a short summer vacation in Karuizawa for two nights and three days.
I often take a vacation like this.
Well, it's going to be hard from now on.
Mr. Shizuke in front of the summer.
He's wearing tennis shoes.
Shall we go?
Let's go.
Wow.
Because I was a cheerleader.
An unknown incident happened at the high school.
August 14th.
It's amazing, isn't it?
NHK's male staff came to cheer for Koshie with a 8mm video of Chia Girl.
The police said that the shooting was done from a low angle.
Let's move on to the next one.
The next one is Yutan Rush Ska Ska.
This one is also amazing.
It's like NHK, where families and young people who spent their summer holidays in their hometowns and highlands spent their summer holidays.
From Sunday to yesterday, it was at its peak.
Yeah, but it looks like the traffic is getting less and less.
Yeah, yeah.
Ruka-chan, did you go somewhere the other day?
I did!
Where?
Nice.
How about you, Ugo-go?
Where are you from?
Let's go.
Nousatsu model.
Do you know what nousatsu means?
It means to come.
On August 14th, there was a huge panic at the airport in Singapore.
The reason for this was the famous model of the magazine Playboy,
I don't know any of them.
It's a very exciting time for the two of them.
The 200 people are getting ready to go.
Let's move on to the next one.
The first victory of the transformation team, K.I.R.
The F1 championship was held on the 15th at the Hungarian Grand Prix.
It's amazing.
This is the record for the shortest time in the world.
Let's move on to the next one.
I'm looking forward to the next one.
Let's go to the next one.
Let's go!
That's right.
I'm sorry.
The last one is amazing.
Punch-kun is already in a bad mood.
He's not in a good mood.
It's been a week since the last live broadcast.
Let's see if we can get through this wave safely and get a lot of attention from all directions.
Where is it?
You're not young anymore?
Well, I wonder.
I'm looking forward to seeing Punch-kun.
Well, let's go home.
I'm looking forward to tomorrow.
See you tomorrow!
What is this?
Today we have Yodai, Furuchofu, Nelton Piken, Asadake, Akahideka and Inoue.
Ugoru Tenki Oho!
Ame ni mo kaze ni mo make nai tsuyoi aite
Good morning!
It's time for Planet's weather forecast.
First, the weather in Naha.
Today's weather in Naha is sunny and cloudy.
Next, Fukuoka.
Fukuoka is a place where the rain and the thunder are in full swing.
It's better not to walk outside with your navel out.
Now, Kochi.
The weather in Kochi is cloudy and rainy.
Hiroshima.
It's raining in Hiroshima.
Where did the sun go?
In Osaka, it's cloudy and sometimes it's raining.
In Koshien, it's raining so much that you want to run away.
In Nagoya, it's cloudy and it rains from noon.
In Nagano, it's cloudy and it rains from time to time.
Now, we're in Tokyo where Ugo-go and Ryuga-chan are.
The weather in Tokyo is cloudy.
It rains once in the morning and once at night.
Will there be no more hot summer?
It's Niigata.
It rains in Niigata.
It's cloudy in Sendai as well.
The weather in Sapporo is sunny.
It's cloudy from noon.
The weather is gloomy all over the country today.
It's raining so much that we can't make plans for the summer vacation.
On the 25th of next week, there will be a concert at Oginome Yoko.
Please come!
I'm going to play with Toru-chan!
Shina's Shuto Special!
Oh, what a coincidence.
We're going to the camp too, poor thing.
I can't believe it!
Good morning.
I'm Yomiuri Betty's Takeda-san.
Today, I'm going to teach you how to be a leader.
I'm a leader!
When you shoot, you have to look at the ball well and aim for the side of the ball.
If you follow the rules, you will naturally be able to go in the right direction.
I would like to follow the rules with great care.
The way I practice is to go against the wall.
If I can go against the wall even if I'm alone, I think I can do it naturally.
I hope you can do well in shooting.
Even if you don't shoot well in the game,
Even if you make a mistake, you have to shoot with the feeling that you are scoring a point.
Don't forget to study literature.
Don't forget to study technology, basics, and your mental state.
I can shoot, so please shoot a good shot.
Please shoot with the feeling that you have definitely decided.
Ah!
Oyajimishi!
Dodo Ryuga!
Sapporo no Rubik's Day!
I'm looking forward to it!
Stop it...
Hadakadetaku!
Good morning.
I'm Furuya Kizakawa.
This week, we'll be talking about dinosaurs.
The dinosaurs are a group of reptiles that appeared 2.3 billion years ago.
Some people think that all the reptiles that lived long ago were dinosaurs, but they're wrong.
The winged dragon that flies in the sky.
The long-necked dragon that swims in the water.
The fish dragon that looks like a fish.
These are not dinosaurs.
Dinosaurs are reptiles that walk with their legs straight down.
I see.
This is called direct fire.
That's what they say.
Dinosaur don't move their legs like a crocodile or a lizard.
It walks like a dog or a bird.
Now that I think about it, all the reptiles nowadays...
I think it's always good to stand up and walk.
See you tomorrow.
I don't know what to do with you!
Oh, son.
Oh, oh.
It's a live broadcast, so it's not a mystery.
Actually, I heard a scary story from a friend on TV.
It's scary just to say it.
It's a morning meeting.
Are you two peeing?
Are you okay?
Today's friend is Yuji Yamashina from Tokyo and Edo.
Good morning, Yuji!
Good morning!
Is today's story scary?
It's scary.
It's scary just to hear that the stage is this one, isn't it?
Then, please.
I heard from a friend that there was a woman named Mijel.
This man picked up a taxi after a long time.
When he got on the Aoyan-buchi... Aoyan-buchi?
For some reason, he was flying.
Yes.
As a father, Mr. Atsuhiro woke up from the shock.
Yes, why?
What happened?
Oh, don't ask me that!
If you listen to it again, you won't be able to see it yet.
The train is about to stop.
This is not a love story.
He said, it's not him.
Soon after he got out of the grave, the man's face was separated.
If you ask the driver, the man who was caught in the cemetery is looking for the culprit.
That's scary.
How about you, Luka?
Huh?
What?
It's funny.
It's not funny, is it?
It's very scary, isn't it?
Thank you very much.
I'm scared and I don't have time, so I can't hold it in anymore.
Can I end it now?
Thank you!
Oh, that was scary.
I got it!
Hit it!
What are you doing?
Good morning!
This week, I'm going to do a love cupid, so please look forward to it!
Today's first day of Naya Bell Otome is Ito Mari from Saitama prefecture!
Hello!
Good morning, Mari-chan!
Good morning!
Good morning.
What grade are you in?
I'm in 5th grade.
What kind of person are you in love with?
He's a sportsman.
Oh, really?
Are you in the same class?
Yes.
So, what should I call you?
O-kun.
Eh?
O-kun?
So, what do you think about O-kun?
I like him.
That's right!
Where is it?
I know where it is!
Mari-chan!
Yes?
I'll do my best to tell Toma and Oh-kun!
Yes.
Well then, Oh-kun!
Oh-kun!
Yes.
Good morning!
Good morning.
Did you hear what I just said?
Yes, I did.
How was it?
How was it for you, Oh?
Well...
Peek-a-boo!
Eh?
I mean, it's normal.
You're shy, aren't you?
I know!
You can't say that you like me!
O-kun, yoroshiku ne!
Mari-chan to nagayaku suru no yo!
Yoroshiku ne!
Now, let's sing a song for the two of them!
A song that everyone wants to hear!
You can give me your love, but it's a tragedy!
If it's for love, I won't give it to you.
It's a love of passion!
Let's do it!
Oku, do your best!
And everyone, bye bye!
See you tomorrow!
Let's do our best!
Bye!
What the hell is this?
What?
What is it?
A pocket.
A musical.
I heard that you guys are doing a great job.
NHK seems to have a lot of things they like.
Thank you for the meal!
Kojiro, Ojo-chan, Gabi, Futsu, Oroda, Futsu, together makes 12.5 million yen!
Why don't you pay me 1,100 yen?
You say that too, Chiyaki
Oh-cha!
With a one-million-yen coin in my hand, let's go fishing!
Ya-ho-ho!
What are you going to do when you're dumb?
I'm going to do it!
Well, well, well, I thought I'd get kicked out of Kiyomizu's stage today, so I'll give you 500 yen.
500 yen?
That's a lot of money today.
I'll give it to you.
You're such an idiot!
Nagaraku-kun, thank you so much for being with us.
Tomorrow will be even more fun, so please look forward to it.
Well then, everyone on Earth, goodbye!
Seira Oyajimu
I'm the bad guy, Osaka Robo.
I'm Tsukiyo's father.
Instead of Tsukiyo, I'm your father.
Don't call me your father!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Good morning, morning!
This is Tony the Summer Man's song album.
The first guest of this summer's live show is a passionate singer, Taichi Ofiteki-san.
The singer is, of course, Big D!
Yeah!
While blowing on the wind, the sky is clear blue sky
Let's sing a song of joy
Oh, okay, okay.
Now you're something more.
Let's put our voices together and get ready for tomorrow.
Today is a good day.
One, two, three!
It's the best!
It's the best, isn't it?
Well then, Torii-kun's number 7, Godrash.
Today's request is a passionate storm in My Flyer's Fideki.
I decided to sing My Friend on my own, but can I?
Hideki, can you sing a passionate song?
If you wish, Hideki!
Can I give you my life?
It's Hideki, not Shideki.
Okay, okay.
Hideki.
I see.
Thank you very much!
Please give him a big hand!
Please look forward to the song album of Tony, the summer man tomorrow as well.
There are a lot of guests who are looking forward to it.
See you tomorrow, boy!
Boy!
Ganbare!
Oh, no!
You have to grow up soon.
I'm jealous.
It's time for the live broadcast of April!
Let's go!
And today, I'm going to hear the anger of the dissatisfied people all over the country!
The first dissatisfied person today is Hamamatsu's Saito Maki-chan!
Maki-chan!
How you doin'?
Okay, Makise, go!
Fumanda!
I got a B in my first year of high school!
I see!
That's so frustrating!
But whose fault is that?
I don't know.
I see!
Good luck, Maki-chan!
See you!
Bye-bye!
Let's go!
Okay, let's go next!
It's Sayaka, the black-eyed girl from Okayama!
Sayaka!
Good morning!
Let's sing a song of dissatisfaction!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10
Good!
Sayaka-chan, you go first!
No matter how many times I practice, I can't sing Private Child's song.
Really?
That's hard, isn't it?
You know a lot of things, don't you?
Sing for us!
That's right!
You have to work hard and practice!
There's still a long way to go.
Yes!
You can do it!
If you're still dissatisfied, keep saying it!
Yes!
Well then, Sayaka-chan, bye bye!
Bye bye!
Bye-bye!
Alright, let's sing again!
Everyone in the studio, ready?
Way to go!
I don't want to!
Well, I heard that Shurikun mistakenly called NHK a national broadcast.
I wonder who it is!
Yeah, it's Tarasami!
Who is it?
It's Mawakoron Brothers!
Zoom in!
How was the first day of the live broadcast?
For the time being, today has just begun.
Tomorrow morning, TV-kun will be at your home again.
Tenebi-kun will return to the studio!
Was it fun?
I think that was the most fun.
Which one was the most fun?
The song!
The song?
That's right, the real Saijo Hideki-san was really cool.
Hosokawa Fumie, Hayashi Atei, Paco, Magokoro Brothers, thank you so much for today!
There are a lot of interesting things tomorrow, right?
It's okay, right?
Bye!
See you tomorrow!
See you on the live broadcast!
Bye-bye!
Hello, hello, how are you all doing?
August 28th, Saturday... Eh?
A little more to this side?
Eh?
Good?
OK!
August 28th at 8pm!